[music]
Hello.
Am I Audible? Not sponsored.
I am Audible. Not sponsored. Wonderful.
All right, everyone. Welcome back or
not. Welcome back, depending on your
situation.
It is time to enter the hot spring. So,
please respectfully remove all your
clothing right now, this instant.
Wherever you may be, you are not
supposed to wear clothing into a
hotring.
Is everyone now respectfully or
disrespectfully
unclothed? Okay. [laughter]
How's How's the volume by the way?
Before it might be very echoey in here.
You're around heavy machinery. All the
more reason to remove thy clothing so
you may sweat and glisten without any
sort of limitations on your skin.
Perfect.
Let us go ahead and prepare Z sounds.
I don't know how well you can hear that
actually
this.
You hear that? It's supposed to be like
water. It sounds relaxing. Wonderful.
Ah, like a beautiful piece of art as I
stretch out my the art frame. All right.
Noveites.
Um, you may well as you know as you know
I am a female. So all the male Navalites
you go on the other side. Okay. like
away from here.
Only only masher only the female novels
may enter the sea. [laughter]
It's it's just a rule, guys. You
understand, don't you? I can't be I
can't be in the same water and liquid as
the people with extensions down there.
All right. Wonderful. Okay. Where are my
pretty novels?
Where is Where is everyone?
Let me let me make you zoom in. Let me
make you appear at the slowest
slowest setting possible cuz it'd be
funny.
There
you're here. Okay. Thank you, my female
noveites.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Female. Female no. Oh.
Oh my gosh, female novelete. Wow, you're
looking so majestic. I can't wait to
have our little girl talk. Male noveles,
you're in a different side. Sorry you
can't see your body, but I'm sure you
can hear the echoes from here.
I'm I'm sure you can hear all of us, you
know, quite well. And now, let me go
ahead and present myself as well. Uh,
let me see. [clears throat]
Let me also show up at the slowest
possible setting for it would be the
funnies.
Oh, wow. This is This is embarrassing.
[laughter]
Hello. Hello there, beautiful.
How How are you?
Let me also
Yeah. There you go. There you go. Hello
there. I am back from my travels. I have
slammed my way through so many states
just to get back home to you, my female
novey. [crying]
How is everyone?
How are you guys doing?
You're going to peek. You're not allowed
to peek. I'm going to have to No, no
peeking. I am only allowed to slither
around the female noveles. I cannot
slitter on your body.
You will have to ask your novel neighbor
to moisturize you with her snaily skin.
[laughter]
But yeah, I guess I am back. Uh not
actually I do have pictures, but I
actually don't know if I can share them
since we have went to
copyrighted places in the time that we
did have. It's really fun though. I had
a fun trip. How did you guys enjoy the
concert too? Oh, right. How many of you
found the the little gifts out of
curiosity? Did you find 11? Was it? I
sent um
I had was it 10? I think it was nine on
the second day and maybe 10 on the first
day, but I know you guys also posted
pictures of that. I just don't know
about the first day. Enjoyable concert.
That's good. I hope you like my MC's as
well. It was 19 total. Yeah, although I
couldn't. There was nine on day two.
Yeah, I wasn't sure how many people
caught day one. Then you found all 19.
Oh, wonderful. You found 12. You found
12. Okay. Nuon.
Oh, no. I'm sorry to hear that, Mecca.
Pokei blank. What she looks like? What
do you mean? She looks like this.
I'm sorry you got sick, though. It was
amazing. That's good. The Zeta. Oh,
yeah. It was really It was really funny.
>> [crying and gasps]
>> I I like the memes about it because she
looked like so horrified while CeCe was
there.
Welcome back and brawl. Thank you. Thank
you. I'm glad you had fun. 12 of us from
chat have some. Yeah, I think Entie was
It was Entie, right? Or was a novel
knife? I think it was the same. Um they
gave a bunch of the envelopes away if I
remember correctly. She was shocked. It
was really funny. I felt bad for her,
too. [laughter]
That was good. I can't remember if we
said the last joke cuz we we did like
one practice session for the MC stuff
and then there was this part [music]
where the staff said, "Are you sure you
want you guys want to mention this? It
might be a little
questionable." And then and then we were
like, "No, I should be fine." [laughter]
Did was there an American comment out of
curiosity? Just say yes or no. That's
all I need.
That's adorable. You met Woomy. You must
out Wooie. He forgot his envelope in
your car. Oh, [laughter]
that's okay. We can forgive Boommy here.
You had an emergency. I'm so sorry to
hear that. I hope that everything's
going okay now, though. You like
breaking down? I'm glad. That's that
song and dance is hard. I don't
understand anything. [laughter]
But Zeta was like really nice about it.
So, I was like, I'm just going to wing
it at this point. Ingram, thank you for
the SCA.
Yeah, I saw some of your pictures, too.
You guys went eating and stuff and you
guys had like a whole meeting at one of
the restaurants, I believe. Oh, the big
red heart. Yeah, I really like that. I'm
glad it turned out well. It's like, hi.
Hi. Hi.
You don't recall American. Okay, maybe
that's for the best. [laughter]
It's probably for the best cuz we were
just keeping an eye on the time. Um,
oh yeah, here's here's one of the
things. When we were doing the make a
triangle thing, what we actually meant
was we wanted all of the audience to
make the hol life triangle, right? So
outside would be like the white uh glow
sticks or pen lights and then the middle
people. This is where you were kind of
meant to fail. You were actually
supposed to make one gigantic green
triangle like the Holive logo, but but
it was kind of hard to time and I think
it was kind of hard to describe. So you
guys kind of did win the making a
triangle with your own like body parts.
So it was okay. We decided like, oh, you
know what? Let's let them have this.
Let's let them have this. It would have
been difficult. I know that was kind of
the point cuz we were going to end in sh
We were going to end with a little pew
pew at the end no matter what. But at
least we would have reason to justify
the pew pew because you lost. [laughter]
[crying]
So that was the the whole theme about
it.
Oh no. Oh, tube. You're using scissors
to eat. Oh, nice. Oh, soft food diet
sucks, man. I'm sorry to hear about the
dentures. Pickle, I did see you lost
your voice. Thanks for coming, by the
way. I appreciate seeing all your like
your tweets about the excitement and
stuff. Incredible violence.
Oh, yeah. You like this, Naval.
[laughter]
Oh, look at you.
Oh, where am I actually? Is this me?
Okay, this is Oh, yeah. Yeah. I'll I'll
moisturize you later, Discord kitten.
But right now, let's let's chat a
little. You know, it's been a while.
It's been a while. Uh let's see. Let me
go through my pictures. We'll go day by
day. We actually did arrive quite early,
so we did have some time to do things.
Let's start with
Okay. Yeah, I did the Twitter space
already. And then we had like the the
party at Zeta's room.
I have a picture right here. I never did
post it. I should post it in a couple
post or something. We ordered Well,
actually, it was her. What happened was
that she was jetlagged pretty badly. So,
she was passed the freak out for most of
the day. And by the time that Z and Kobo
were already awake, it was really late.
And they were like, "Well, we missed
dinner, so now what?" And I told him,
"Oh, you could you could order
something. It is completely in your
capabilities to order. So, I we ended up
going for pizza. For some reason, they
really wanted to try like the was it the
In-N-Out stuff and they were really
excited about Target and Walmart,
[laughter]
which I thought was really funny. In
fact, I think on one of the days they
woke up early just to see Target and I'm
like, "Okay."
Yeah. literally like, "Yeah, the
American Experience. It must be Walmart
and Target. I want to see what it's
like." And I told him like, "You got to
pronounce it as Tar J. You know, make it
fancy." Tar J. We're heading to the Tar
J.
She's talking about it. I know. It's so
funny. I think they woke up like 7 or 6
a.m. or something just to get there. I
was like, "Okay."
It is very adorable. So, we ordered some
some food. She had like a garlic, some
sort of garlic bread, which was funny.
Funny enough, it was bigger than the
pizza. I also didn't expect the garlic
bread to be that huge. The fries were
super good. I was uh very impressed with
it. I did not expect a lot of spices
from a typical pizza brand that I shall
not mention just in case. But I didn't
expect them to season it that way. I
didn't even know they had fries seasoned
like that.
Thank you, Novas. Oh, hey. Okay, I've
seen your tweets. Thank you so much. I'm
glad that you enjoyed your time, too.
That's okay. That's okay, Mimi. No
worries.
Same as the UK does. The The fries were
super good. The only issue is like they
didn't give a lot of ketchup, but the
seasoning carried it. I think it had
like a little bit of a lemon a lemon
zest to it. So, some spice, pepper, and
maybe a little bit of lemon. Uh the only
thing is that we didn't really have
plates. We were actually eating off on a
a chair. [laughter]
So, all of that was on top of her chair
and it was kind of leaning against her
bed. Uh it was Kobo who did it. But
number one, Kobu dropped my fork first
off, but that's okay. I had spares. And
then she ended up like getting some some
ketchup onto her bed and she was like,
"Oh no, what should we do? It looks kind
of like blood." And is it like you got
to you got to dab it. You're not
supposed to rub it all over the thing.
You have to dab it carefully otherwise
it's going to be really sticking there.
Tiger match was fine. Thank you. Thank
you. I'm glad. Yay.
Did I eat the burger? H there's no
burger in that that first night though.
I think I think that was the only thing
I really ate on the first time because I
was still really just I ate the the
airport food. So, I was like, you know
what? This is probably enough for me. I
got I got to go diet again, man. Every
time I come back from trip, I got to go
diet, but it's not that bad. So,
I'm Well, yeah, I I did not eat the
crust, actually. I don't think No, no,
no. I ate one crust. I tried to be
respectful about it. I ate one crust,
but the rest of it is like, nah. Two
tiny pizzas. That's good enough for me.
And then
I think that was pretty much it for that
one day because we were we were all just
arriving and people were jetlagged. I
know the others went to they also went
to Target.
Yeah. Okay. Next picture.
The hotel room. It was It was nice, but
it was kind of incomplete thinking about
it. The bed was super comfy. Like I just
I just wanted to pass out onto it. It
was so good. It's so good. In fact, that
I'm pretty sure like when Zeta was
jetlagged on that first day, she I think
roomkeeping was actually going to into
her room and she was freaked out. She
was like, "Roomkeeping was like so
concerned about me." And I said like,
"Well, yeah, maybe maybe they wanted to
clean your room and then realized you
were there."
And she was just so kind of like zonked
out. I think roomkeeping was even
concerned about her. They gave her free
chocolate though and I said like, "Well,
maybe maybe don't trust the chocolate
just yet because it's kind of suspicious
timing." But then eventually we we
hypothesized that it was just during her
range that she was supposed to clean
though. Yeah.
Hi, welcome and
yeah, I'm glad you like the MC's. I'm
probably not going to continue to curse
to be honest. I think like I think
kisses from that many people over the
course of X years. I think that's
enough.
I think I think that's enough, guys. We
don't have to get into the curse beyond
that.
What else? Oh, yeah. There was like the
the room service or not room service,
but like the snacks they charge you for.
They provided us some snackaroonis and
some water, but the water was really
expensive. Like it's $10 or something
just for a whole whole bottle. You like
it could have slow down. Thank you
midnight. It was super busy. Um
was it really that busy? It's kind of
hard to know because like we were just
kind of stranded in the backstage.
I know AX was really busy though, for
sure.
Uh, I saw like a bunch of tweets. People
were going insane over the lad stuff,
which is hilarious to me. And then I saw
this one tweet making its round where
this girl was stubbing on some dude's
crotch. That was kind of weird, but it's
like okay. So, I think it was fine.
Depending on where you were. Yeah. A
bala. Yeah, it's expensive. Kobo ate
like some of Zeta's snacks. They didn't
realize it was paid for. Like you had to
pay for it if you took some. But I told
him like, "Yeah, it's actually weighted.
Um, because you took like this amount of
snacks from it, it might charge it based
on the amount you took, not the entire
price." But I I cannot confirm. I told
him you might as well eat it. You know,
the company's already gotten it. You had
fun. I'm glad. Woo! Woo! You forgot your
envelope, though. But I forgive you. Hi,
Idia. Welcome back. Yeah, for those who
don't know, I did some voice lines for
Denia attack. is already already there,
but I think it is. You will have to see
it for yourself when the game is
launched. And then we have the train
skin, too, which was really nice. They
did art for it. So, you can see all of
the If I remember correctly, I have
really bad memory. I believe the novel
leads are there.
But if I'm wrong, then that was my fault
cuz I don't remember crap. So, yeah,
keep an eye on Denta Attack. It's such a
cool game. I'm really happy they asked
me about it. It's like, yay.
Yeah, Iris is there, too. And I believe
there's some other collabs with other
people. I think it's a mixture of
YouTubers and maybe non YouTubers, but
I'm not entirely sure.
Hello, Mystic. It is 4:00 a.m. Uh, shake
my head. It's okay. At least it's in
your friend's car. You know, I I saw
some people had like a not a good time
leaving the concert. Maybe because of
accidents or someone stealing their crab
and was like, "Oh, no."
But next time if I am to deliver more
things, I'm thinking like it would be
really funny to do something adjacent to
Slender Man. [laughter]
I want to try something horroresque, but
we'll see about it. I'm so glad they let
me do it though. I carried those 19
envelopes. I was like I wasn't sure if
it would be allowed and but I asked
anyway. They were really sure it
wouldn't be happening, but I I end up
getting the approval. She's like, "Oh,
thank God. Otherwise, I have to make
space for my luggage back home."
That's okay, idol. Thank you so much for
watching me. And Richard, hello. I spent
a lot of time. I saw I saw Kuma. You
were very thirsty. [music] The last boot
of ants was the biggest highlight. Man,
I know people were shirtless there and
crazy. [laughter]
You You would have lost the envelope.
Oh,
but yeah.
Uh, let's see. Oh, yeah. Pictures.
Pictures. Hotel room. Really nice bed.
Uh, really glad they have an ironing
board. Otherwise, I would have been
screwed. Shower. Shower's kinky for
whatever reason. [laughter]
I don't I don't know why. They always
get me kinky showers. It's like, okay,
thanks.
I think I think hotels are just freaky.
There must be something about high
establishment hotels that are freaky
deicky cuz this was the same thing with
like New York.
They have the glass wall showers. I
know. It is so confusing to me. It's
very confusing. It's like a literal
window to see you naked. Just like this.
Just like this. Look at you. My little
work of art. Look at my little nove. My
female novey. And of course the male
novelist who are like all the way over
there. Oh, but I can only moisturize one
at a time. But right now, I'm going to
moisturize you. Don't you Don't you not
use your little slime, your snail thing
for your skin.
Do you I don't know how you guys do your
little moisturizing techniques, but you
can actually buy snail mucus. But why
buy snail mucus when I am right here all
for the taking? all to help you
moisturize and glisten with the certain
beautiful radiance that you deserve.
[gasps]
You're happy to possess that
information.
Oh, your skin holds onto the steam so
well. You're like, you're vi not
vibrating, you're vibrant.
I enjoy the way you stay still for me. I
respect that a lot actually. Snails
really, really love things that stay
still.
Oh, the way you breathe so slowly, too.
It's so slow. I can't even see you.
Like, I can't see your your chest shake
that much. Well, maybe if I if you do
this, then yeah, but I think that's your
heart palpitations, girly.
You like my performance? Thank you. I'm
so glad. Oh, good luck with the jet lag.
Thank you for coming, too, by [music]
the way. It just feels wrong to watch.
You shouldn't be watching if you're a
male.
[laughter]
It's okay. It's okay, male. No, you can
join in as well. But you have to leave
your goods at the door. [laughter]
Yeah, you you have to leave your goods
at the door and then we can accept you
here. So, maybe just a little little
smack.
You're cheating on me. Thank you,
Greenie.
Are you confused? Don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, you have very calming hands. I enjoy
the way you seem to quiver with fear.
Anyway, anyway, what else
we went to? No pictures allowed, but I
took Oh, man. That's such a shame. But
maybe if I censored this really well. I
lost one of my acrylic stands, though.
I'm so sad. Actually, I I have the
acrylic, but I lost the actual stand
itself. I was like, "Darn it. Darn it."
So, I don't know where that's gone. I
actually have a feeling it's at the
venue. So, whoops. That's okay. Once I
get my my own chibiella, I could use
that and I will not lose it. That's such
a shame. Such a shame. But yeah, we went
to to Disney. Apparently, they're
celebrating their 70 years.
um took a picture of a random bear.
Oh yeah, that's right. We kept using the
fastpass. Thankfully, Liz is really good
at knowing how to navigate the Wizy. She
was always like, "Okay, we'll use the
fastass here and then we'll go over
here." And she was just leading us like
a Girl Scout trip. Yeah. 70 years.
You lost something, Doc. You lost your
shirt, didn't you? the the advent shirt,
not your actual shirt. You're tired,
Phil. Oh. Oh. Oh, no. I'm sorry to hear
that.
Oh, Faulk.
But yeah, we went with
Mo Chan and Watan or Senpai.
I like saying Chan. We went to like the
the aerial trip. Took a lot of pictures.
I Oh, yeah. I sat with Zeta for this
one. I also wore something really stupid
for that day, which I was so proud of,
by the way.
Let's see.
LC Lapen is giving a shout out to the
person who met at the cosplay photo
meetup. Yeah, they brought a shior
standy. That's hard to bring. They're
big, aren't they? Did he get anything? I
was debating on it, but I think I ended
up getting nothing from it.
I was debating on getting a uh for some
reason
Kermit Kermit the Frog was being sold
there along with Miss Piggy. I I was
kind of surprised. I didn't know they
belonged to the to the W Disney. And
then Zeta was really into the Lilo and
Stitch stuff. So, I kept trying to tell
her, "You should buy this. This right
here, limited time. Don't you want to
adopt him? I know you want to adopt
him." She's like, "But I I don't really
need him." It's like, "But you want to
adopt him. Limited time. You're not
going to see it elsewhere. It's only in
America. You should get it. [laughter]
She's a Disney adult like in secret. Oh,
it's not even a secret. [laughter]
She's just so good at it. I think she
just like really loves it. It is fun
though. I had a great time at Disney. It
was a little warm though. It's very,
very warm on the day we went to. Then
again, I guess it just happens whenever
the sun's out. They're owned by it. I
had no idea. So yeah, I sat next to her
for the the Disney one.
Oh, that's a blurry picture. I'll delete
that one. That's also a blurry picture.
Wow, that sucks. Oh, that's right.
Because of the dress I wore, I was
basically like glowing in the dark. That
was kind of neat. Oh, that's a good
picture.
Oh, that's a Yeah, that's great. Oh,
man. If only you could see the picture.
My favorite part of the whole mermaid
ride was actually Ursula. Ursula is so
cool. See, I actually am on Ursula's
side. Ariel signed up on that agreement,
man. She basically signed a contract.
You can't complain about losing your
voice now. You signed it, Ariel. What
are you going to do now? [crying]
Thank you, Doc. Yeah, I am really glad
with how everything turned out. I was
actually kind of nervous about it
because I don't really sound good for
certain songs. So, every time I have to
yell, I was like, gosh, I'm going to
sound like a dork. But I think it turned
out okay. So, it was like, yay. Thank
God. [laughter]
Thank God. I'm really really glad with
how it turned out. I'm so happy she
chose the song, too. I It's a really fun
song.
Have confidants.
I have no confidence. I'm a snail. Look
at me. I'm I'm just a snail. Okay, I'm
going to moisturize you just a little
bit. Let me Let me get on top. Cabadons
you. I'll go right here. Yeah. Yeah. Oh,
right there.
I like the way your your hair drips in
the water. I could watch it drift for
hours. You can't see your hair, but
trust me, I can see all of it.
All right, so we went to the cars thing.
Oh, this was kind of funny. So Zeta and
Ko kept getting lost and I kept having
to watch out for them. Not necessarily
lost, but because they were taking
pictures of everything, they end up
being like lagging behind. And then the
others were kind of like ahead because
they were navigating or just like
translating stuff. So I would be in the
middle trying to wave my hands for Coobo
and Zeta to catch up and be like, "Come
here, children. Come on, guys. We got to
go. We can't GET LEFT BEHIND.
[laughter]
I THOUGHT IT WAS so silly. It's really
happy. It's like nice seeing them like
that though. And Koko's so funny. She's
like she acts like a middle schooler,
which is probably why she gets treated
like one.
So she's a dork. Yeah. So we did that.
They kept falling behind. Oh, this was
this was really fun. I wonder
I did I can't show it. I did take a
view. Hold on. Let me let me mute myself
[music] so I can hear this.
Okay. Yeah. So, this is like one of my
favorite rides that happened and uh
thankfully I I recorded my experience,
but it's just for my personal enjoyment.
So, there's this car ride where you get
into an actual car or something that
looks like a car and they just sort of
drive you around. For some reason, I
don't know if they were serious about
this. They were like, "Who has a
license? I can't drive." I think they
might have thought we were actually
going to control the car.
So, I sat with uh Kobo and Zeta for this
one.
And Kobo was also was also really into
recording everything.
So, it starts off as the story of cars,
which I've never watched, by the way.
I've never seen cars before. So, a lot
of it kind of went over my head, but it
seems like my understanding is they're
they're they're a bunch of cars. Yeah.
Yeah. And I think he's like tired of
being a boring car who does nothing. He
wanted to race. So, you start off with
his slice of life, his evolution from
becoming a watcher to now a racer, and
then you go to the actual race section,
and that's when the ride actually gets
hectic. It was so fun. I really enjoyed
it. You went like in a fast speed, and
you're supposed to sort of like quote
race the other car next to you, which
was uh Liz's group, which had the JP
Senpaiis and Risa. And then I'm pretty
sure we won. [laughter]
I'm pretty sure I'm pretty sure we won
though. Well, it was nice. And it's like
it goes up and down and the speed was
perfectly fine. It was just so good. And
it's so great to have the fast pass. I'm
so freaking happy about it because I
hate waiting in lines and it's not too
expensive. Well, it probably racks up.
It definitely racks up.
So, but it was nice.
We rode in lightning. I think so,
actually. I wonder if there's a picture.
No, actually, they were generic cars.
Now that I look at it, they were generic
blue cars.
So, it was not actually the the
characters itself. Oh, I can't show this
one, but I wish I could, but it has our
hands on it. Um, I believe Zeta and I
bought ice cream, but we were supposed
to go on a ride immediately. So, it was
like, "Well, we're gonna wait here and
eat." So, they had to wait on us and and
then we were told like, "Yeah, you're
going to have to let the spa out first,
but I was like, no, I want to eat it
now." But I I still ended up having to
wait for it to because I had to like I
already opened it. I ate a little of
what I could and then I had to put it
back in my my little purse. Uh, some of
the chocolate got into my purse and had
to like Oh, does anyone have alcohol
wipes? So, thankfully Latenai had some
wipes, so that saved my butt. Although,
I think the states are still kind of
like, if you know where to look, they're
still kind of there. I wonder if I can
still clear it out. I'm just glad he
didn't get on any of my plushies. If
they got on my plushies, I would destroy
myself.
Really good, though. Freak. I love
chocolate covered bananas. They're so
good. I think they're my favorite
dessert now. And then for Z, she just
got like a regular
Mickeyshaped ice cream.
And then let's see, there are two sides
to the W Disney actually. There's the
the dedicated Disney side and one that's
more like I think it had the Pixar,
which is why it had the Cars thing, I
guess. Or is is cars Pixar or is that
just Disney?
Yeah.
Uh, Amelia, welcome back in cyborg.
I'm glad you liked it. Thank you. Thank
you.
Uh, let's see. Oh, this is kind of
stupid. I took a picture of Zeta taking
a picture of like random stuff.
[laughter]
[crying]
It's like, might as well. And then there
was a little horse ride. We didn't get
on it, though.
I don't even think it needs a horse.
It's like a trolley with a horse
attached to it. Why? I legit think like
they did not need it. There's no way. I
think that truly could have ran by
itself. I think the horse was just like
there to take a walk.
Hi, Unben.
No, I am not I'm not a heron
protagonist. No. As I oh increase myself
just to to look at you lovingly, my
novel.
No. And it's it's just it was just an
accident. No worries about it.
E I'm just a little snaily, you know.
I'm just a little snail.
It was really fun. I liked it.
M Dolan and Goopy.
Oh,
I just realized.
Thank you, Epsilon.
Let's see.
Took a picture. Oh, yeah. I was debating
on buying a Goofy plush. Gosh, Goofy is
so funny. Oh, and there's a Star Wars
section. Okay, now I clearly do not know
much about Star Wars.
Um, we went on one of the the rides.
Actually, the rides kept breaking down,
which is kind of funny cuz the first
time I could excuse, right? And
thankfully the first ride it broke down
when it was already like we're kind of
over with it. We had only a little bit
of a weight, but it wasn't too bad. You
know, we had cooling.
Yeah, it breaks down a lot. I was kind
of surprised.
So, we did that. We actually did it like
twice because it broke down there. They
said like, "Well, you can now have an
extra fast pass, so feel free to do
whatever." So, we just ended up going
there twice for some reason. It is
really nice, though. Oh, and the the
ride itself has a little bit of a story.
Um, I believe it is I I was not aware of
this, but I think Rea told me like,
"Yeah, so that dude is actually Han Solo
or Han Solo and Leia's son." And I was
like, "Well, why is he evil?"
But I don't know what he looks like
under the mask. So every time he shows
up to be evil, I'm like, "Yes, yes, take
me." And Liz is like, "What the frig?"
He had issues. Kylo Ren. Yeah. I don't
know anything about Kylo Ren. Why is he
evil though?
Yeah, I found that out. So he's like
what? He's Luke's uh nephew or
something. Legion, welcome back. back.
I'm glad you liked it. My MC tradition.
We got to break the curse though. I
can't just keep making out [laughter]
with tongue. I saw her and welcome back
an army dog. Hope you're having a good
time at the gym. He wasn't treated well
as a kid. Is it cuz his parents died? I
heard that like Leia died from
heartbreak and Han Solo just quit.
[laughter]
Well, Han Solo he had an epic death, I
think. So, they they got married. Luke
tried to kill him. Why? He killed his
dad. Why?
Actually, you know what? Which movie is
this? I've only seen the first Star Wars
movie. And maybe like the one with the
the girl as a female character
as the main character. His uncle had a
vision of him being evil and Luke being
the master Jedi decided murder was the
only solution. So, this is Luke's fault.
Who writes Star Wars?
Is it Steven Spielberg? Did he write
Star Wars?
Why did he just make it? What's the
difference?
The for Oh, George Lucas. Wait, what
does Stephen Spielberg do then?
[laughter]
Okay, so he's the writer. Steven
Spielberg does
what exactly?
No, he did ET.
Really? He did ET? Okay. ET is going to
be a different story then. They're
friends. Okay. Okay. Sorry, I don't know
media, guys. I don't know anything. I'm
Baby the the sequel. I see. Well, that's
why they also tried to give it to a
different generation
from my understanding. He made ET
Jurassic. I still I don't think I even
watch Jurassic Park, guys, which is so
funny cuz I really wanted to see it ride
in uh Universal Studios. Thank you,
Kaizen. I'm glad you enjoyed it. Hans
Devil's long overdue. I heard he didn't
like it. Yeah, he's been done since his
first appearance. I heard about that,
too. Mega Man, welcome back.
What? Why did you say no? It's super
good. Yeah, but they've had like 10
Jurassic Parks. How many dinosaurs do
they need to revive? It's okay. We can
watch it someday.
Oh, don't forget we're going to do
Street Fighter watch along tomorrow with
Bibbs.
And then hopefully Yofi can also
reschedu her thing.
But I'm going to do a different one with
her since I I was actually uh going to
ask her as well. But time schedules
conflict
original. Oh, that's so many numbers, my
dude. I know Reese is an expert at Star
Wars stuff. Oh, actually, there's
something. Okay. Okay. Let me look at
the picture. Oh, right, right. Okay.
Okay. I was so happy about this.
Humoko and I, we were able to see. Wait,
was it with this one? No, I think it was
with the Wookie. I saw Darth Vader. God,
I wish he hugged me. Why didn't he hug
me? I saw Darth Vader just walking by.
It must have been super hot underneath
all that helmet and stuff. He just has
to hug me without ever taking off his
clothes, but he was so cool. He was so
polite, too. He didn't kill anyone on
his way. And then after that, I think
the girls went to look for um a Oh,
yeah. That's right. We separated because
they had to look for a bathroom and we
were still waiting on people to finish
their shopping and that's what happened.
Let's see. This picture sucks. I'm going
to delete this one. Some got in my way.
This is the ride that broke down. Me
going like, "Yeah."
Oh, this is Oh, man. Some got in the
way. My picture. It's a picture of the
Wookie. He hugged me, guys. He hugged
me. He hugged Mo, too. Actually, was it
Mo? Yeah, it was. Gosh,
too bad I don't have a good picture
about it. People kept getting in the
way. This kid's in my way. This woman's
in my way. That's just the back of the
Wookie.
The only picture I have is literally his
mouth. He was too tall.
[crying]
Get out of my way. How can I see my
Wookie who I don't know anything about?
Oh, wait. It's Chewbacca. Who's the
Wookie then? Sorry, I wasn't looking. I
was looking at the pictures. Is the
Wookie and Chewbacca different people?
[laughter] Am I like Dart Raven? Is that
a different dude? They're the same.
Okay. He is the Wookie. Oh, okay. Okay.
Chewbacca is Wookie is Chewbacca's
species. So, Chewbacca is specifically a
Chewbacca, but the Wookie is like his
whole race. Okay. Okay. No, Wookie's a
species. Good heavens. This is so much
lore.
Let me check.
Hi.
Hello.
Hi there.
How do you someone someone do Japanese
for me? How do you say tell tell Mochi
hi?
Slime to see you too, Space Ace King. I
saw your tweets. Thank you so much for
enjoying the show. And Tim, you cut
ahead of 50 people. Check in. Oh my
gosh. Oh,
that's your JP level. Oh my gosh.
Someone put in a non-transation.
Unfortunately, my my extensions keep
translating everything.
E in [__] Japan. E someone put in a
roachi, please. Thank you, sir. Welcome
back. But I was so glad I got to hug him
as someone who doesn't even know much
about Star Wars. Oh, now we had a lot of
beignettes. Liz paid for it, thank God.
And I had some food. There's too much
food to be honest, but we walked so
much, so it was really deserved.
Um
I'm a fully welcome.
Let's see. There's a uh Oh, there the
other Star Wars ride. Okay, so the first
one you just kind of go into some
vehicle and you're supposed to escape
it. That's one of the rides that broke
down. The other ride, and I assume this
is the only other Star Wars ride. It's
the one where you pilot like an aircraft
and there's like a whole mini game where
you're supposed to navigate with
everyone else. So, you're like a team.
You have the engineers,
um, people who shoot and people who
drive. Risa and I were the drivers. I
could only go up and down and she could
only go left and right. People were
backseating so hard. They were like
left, right, up and down. But the thing
is, you couldn't actually control it
without like some sort of prompt. You
had to wait for the prompt to show up.
And if you did it too early, it doesn't
quite count. We did pretty well, though.
At least I thought we did.
There was a Star Wars Christmas special.
I'll think about it. Like, welcome back.
It's easier with less people. Well, you
kind of needed everyone though because
you everyone had a specific function.
Like, you couldn't do this with just uh
two people cuz then no one would shoot.
Did you go to the pirates? I don't think
so. Now that I think about it, we might
have skipped that one.
I'll tell you if I see it, but I'm
pretty sure we did not. Our score was
around
27,000 though, which I think is okay. I
think it was fine.
Oh, there's that weird catfish looking
monster for the ride as well. [music] We
went here twice.
Oh, what else? Oh, and there's this Oh,
we end up getting some sort of pineapple
ice cream. It was actually really good.
We waited a bit because it was also
hosting a show and the show is a bunch
of uh birds up in the air. Not real
birds, they're animatronics. But they
start singing songs for you. Some sort
of Hawaiian theme. It was really pretty.
I liked it. It's unfortunate, but there
was this one song that I should have
Shazammed, but I didn't do it in time.
The Dole Whip. Oh, is that what it's
called? I think so. Kamoko were really
into it. The Tiki Lounge. Yeah, that's
what it was. Mhm. They let us into some
sort of um Hawaiianish themed room, very
nicely airond conditioned.
[laughter] I I still sat with Kobo and
Zade and the other girls were like over
here because we were such a big group so
we had to split up. But I was like, I
have a really good viewing here. I'm not
moving. So, we just stayed put.
[laughter]
It's a really good room. I'm surprised.
Oh, and then they had fascinating
lights. And so basically all the
animatronic birds, they would uh just
chirp a little, move around. There's
this little water fountain in the
middle. That was wonderful. It's my
favorite picture actually. Gosh, that's
great. And then uh around the room, the
totem poles also sing. Their mouths
move.
So that was cool. I did say on the later
songs, uh they were singing a Hawaiian
war chant for whatever reason. So it's
like, huh? Okay. Maybe they hate us.
Okay.
And then what else?
Oh, yeah. Okay. So, this was like after
things were done. I got to go to
Universal Studios. It was really great.
I do still think that between the two
though, I will actually lean towards
Disney. Disney had really good rides.
I think. How many rides did we do? I
know we did two Star Wars. We did a
Little Mermaid.
Was it only that many? I feel like we
did more, but I don't know if I took a
picture. I guess we just walked around
most of the time. We ate a lot of food,
that's for sure.
Yeah. Oh, no. We did the cars. Sorry. We
did cars. So, was it four rides?
No, we actually did not do the Haunted
Mansion. We skipped it cuz that ride was
always always so busy.
Indiana Jones. I think we were
considering going to there, but we
didn't. Yeah,
there's Toy [music] Town and Tombtown. I
don't think I didn't see it. I think we
might have skipped it. But we did split
off at some point, so maybe the others
went there. I know some of us headed
back early just so we could rest up and
not die.
You'll honestly prefer Universal. When I
went to Universal, though, I felt like
it was mostly a VR experience. Um, so
for Universal,
first off, I know nothing. I I went to
the Simpsons place, which was really
cool. I like the whole aesthetic of it.
And this is also when I realized that my
acrylic stand, the stand itself, not the
actual character, you know. Um, that's
when I realized it's gone. I was like,
no.
There was a Simpsons ride. I really
liked the appearance of it. So you
you're going to crusty land just this
giant clown and you go into his mouth.
Now this one I did not do the fast pass.
This was just me and my uh the group of
friends that we were visiting as well.
So we did not do the fast pass. It was a
lot of waiting which is why I highly
recommend if you ever plan on going to
Universal Studios prepare 3 months in
advance cuz this was out of the blue. I
did not expect to go here.
It was like an hours long wait for just
some things unless you got there early
but like by midday it's it's pretty bad.
Yeah. So for Disney, thank gosh we had
Fastpass and Mio was like she's super
sweet. Mio is so funny.
Is it like
Yeah, like good funny. She's so sweet. I
love her. And what senpai is very
what's it say? How do you say she she
seems kind of shy but in a cute way. Shy
in Japanese. [snorts]
There's supposed to be not just has a
kashi. There's another word.
Is it?
I don't know. But she seems very
ladylike. Yeah.
Sheepish.
She's very She's very ladylike.
Thank God for her alcohol wipes. Oh, she
she's funny though cuz I remember when I
was sitting next to her in the car, I
she was like, "Ah, naniasha like what
did you eat?" And she said, "Don't eat
me." [laughter] I said, "Wow,
I'll eat your friends then." She was
like, "Nah, I like I like lamb, so I
might have to eat some.
It's like, "Sorry, but I'll spare you."
But they were very nice. Mio Senai was
so kind to help um help start the Disney
stuff cuz it was her idea.
So anyway, for the Universal Studios
Questy Land, I noticed the difference
between the Disney one and the Univers
Universal Studios. I feel like Universal
Studios actually decorates their waiting
rooms.
The Disney one was mostly a lot of
exterior waiting areas from my my
gathering. Naturally, I didn't go to the
Haunted Manor, so I don't know about
that one. But Universal Studios, you can
kind of see the quality of it. They
basically put like TVs and they repeat
some some shows. I think they're unique
to the area, though.
So, I saw a lot of uh Simpsons decor
like there's this character with ginger
beards uh some doctor looking guy
and uh just that. And then the I didn't
expect this. So, when I went to the
Crusty Land thing, they actually put you
into a little cart. And I think this is
also how they conserve space. So, they
give you like a VR experience without
wearing the VR for this one. They
actually have this gigantic screen and
it plays some sort of animation.
And the cart you're in, it moves along
to the animation. Now, this is the part
where I really think they could have
done more. I think they should have gone
a little bit more extreme with it.
The motion rides, that's what they are.
Yeah.
Google Google Translate.
Welcome back.
So yeah,
um I don't even know these characters,
but the whole plot was like the crusty
guy, the clown, was the jerk to one of
his employees and his employees is out
to get him for revenge. So that was a
whole motif of it. I do like the fact
that because you're there as a viewer,
they kind of try to rope you into the
story. They're like, "How about you guys
join us on the ride?" Yeah. Like, why
don't you join us? It's like It's really
cute. I like it. Sideshow Bob. Oh,
that's his name. But yeah, he's the the
main villain here. Is he actually evil?
I just think he's probably underpaid.
[laughter]
So, it was neat. I I really love the
decor for that. They really like to work
on the aesthetic. I feel like the ride's
not as intense as it could be. He's
evil. Evil. Oh, okay. Oops.
Dang. I see. Huh.
I sympathize with him, too, because I
didn't know he was evil. I just thought
he was like really treated poorly based
on what the ride showed.
Ah, I see. He's psycho and underpaid. A
really bad combination, but probably
better than being like psycho and
overpaid.
That's okay, Ryan. I hope you enjoyed
the VOD. He hates Bart, too. Is it cuz
Bart's evil? H. But yeah, I took a
picture of some of the Springfield
police people. I don't know who they are
either, but they look really nice. Oh,
and then in the Universal Studios, you
can actually do like a tour. It lasts
about an hour and it talks about the
types of movies they made. If you ever
go, I highly suggest trying out the
tour. Especially Well, do it do it when
it's like do the rides first. Maybe you
should do the tour later on because the
tour takes about an hour. So, you better
hold your piston, girl or boy.
It was really worth it though because
like here's the thing. I don't even know
these shows. They had a Back to the
Future sort of um building. You go into
the sets essentially. They have a whole
mini town that is dedicated to just the
sets and they have different buildings
depending on what they need to shoot. So
you go into there, they showed like um
some part from I think King Kong.
Yeah, it was King Kong. Ooh. So you go
into a tunnel and I thought like, oh,
okay, it's a just a tunnel, you know,
spooky. But then when you go in, they
actually surrounded the entire inside of
a tunnel with screens and the the car
itself starts vibrating. There's no seat
belts and you start moving around and
then you have the King Kong fight off
people and he's saving your butt. It's
so It's so cool. Yeah. Look into it. I I
also like put in my memory like Oh my
gosh, he fought a He fought a dinosaur.
It was King Kong, right? Hold on. Let me
let me skip ahead. Let me mute this.
Yeah, there's a bunch of dinosaurs that
showed up and they're like chasing you
and your car is just right there and you
can feel every single vibration and the
left and right turn movements. Yeah, let
me let me skip around. Yeah, it is King
Kong. I don't even know the plot of King
Kong. Apparently, you're in an island
trying to shoot a movie and King Kong
really really likes this one girl, so he
spares her.
So that was neat. Oh, and then beyond
that, you kind of see like how the
scenes, the set stages themselves, they
play with optical illusions. They told
us that the windows at the bottom are
like the biggest and as you go to the
top, they get smaller because you don't
need to see them. And then for some of
the doors, it's really good because they
look so far away. But some of the doors
are just flat. It's just part of the
cardboard cutout. Welcome back, Sikai.
Welcome back. Let me slitter on top of
you now. And Jared, thank you. I'm glad
you liked it. And Sap, thank you for
becoming a novel Knight. For those who
are novel Knights and join just now,
please check out my vlog. I checked out
a Capcom Pom mystery box. Limited time,
so please check it out.
I edited that and then I had help
editing it so I can have more time to do
other stuff. And then there's the other
VODs or the other videos that I've also
edited. So, please check that out as
well.
Um, let's see.
Oh, yeah. And then Universal Studios,
since they're a publishing company, they
had a lot of sets dedicated to other
regions. Like they had this one sort of
Spanish looking section or like a
European
Excuse section.
I wanted to Photoshop myself into some
of these. I don't know if I'd be allowed
to show it. Oh, and then there's this
really cool section. You go into this
metro, a little metro station, and then
they keep you there, and then all of a
sudden they simulate an earthquake,
and everything just starts falling
apart. Like the roof falls, and then
there's like uh you know, when
electricity goes rampant or it goes
crazy, the little sparks of electricity
starts showing up and then a fire
appeared. And then all of a sudden a
gigantic flood appears too. And it was
so cool. I wish I I might still try to
do this. We'll see. I I don't think I
can. But like realistically, what
context we have besides the screen? I
was thinking like if I cut this to only
show the flooding, you guys would
probably think like, "Oh no, is she
already okay? [screaming]
Is she okay? Where is she?" I could have
tweeted something like, "Guys, I have a
bad feeling. What should I do?" And it
is on Twitter.
It would have been funny.
But I I would put a disclaimer. I'm
okay. No worries. I survived. [laughter]
It was so good. They used real water and
like things are starting to fall apart.
It's just amazing. I loved it. This was
like one of my favorite sections.
And then they also showed you the scene
from Jaws, which I also don't know if
I've ever watched. I don't think I did.
Oh, thank you. Right, F. I'm glad you
like it, Kaama. Where's a Kaya? Welcome.
Welcome. The King Kong was a massive
animatronic that attaches to Oh, they
attacks the cart. Oh, wow. Well, they
removed it. It's just 3D now, which is
such a shame. Uh, for the Jaws thing.
Oh, okay. So, the Jaws, uh, you you come
in and you see this guy drown and die. I
was thinking about posting this, too. I
was going to be like, "Guys, I don't
know what's happening. I don't know how
to help this dude.
I was just thinking like maybe I should
post this, but people might actually
think there is a real guy drowning,
which which kind of would be the point.
And then the this fire starts showing
up. I think it's like the the gasoline
or something. It shows up on fire and
then the shark appears.
A sage, thank you so much for the
gifties.
I'm talking about my Universal Studios
experience, which is so cool. And then
they also showed one set. This one
looked a little bit more um I think
Spanishbased. They talked about how they
can simulate weather effects only
specific areas. They also had like a
flash flood as a simulated thing too
which is really interesting. Movie
theater is nuts man. It is nuts.
I'll see if I can do something here.
Oh, and then they had like this whole I
think it's a war of the worlds. I'm not
sure, but they they took us through like
a a wreck of some kind. There was a a
plane that was cut in half, and they
told us that the plane itself was maybe
$200,000.
No, no, no. Maybe like $50,000,
something like that, you know, something
something anyone can afford.
But the actual ability to transport the
plane from point A to point B was like a
million or 200,000, something like that.
Hi, Kobo. Cobo, I miss you. It was so
fun hanging out with you. I hope you had
a great time with all of us. I'm sure
you did. You're so funny.
Schwarz, welcome. Thank you for the SC
and Hal. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
so much for the support ad as well.
Thank you. Thank you.
Yeah, you're sobering. You're sobering.
What? Girl, are you drunk? Okay,
[laughter]
but yeah, let's hang out again at some
point.
Just talking about my stuff.
And then besides the Oh, yeah. They
talked about how they're filming the the
Odyssey here and there's a gigantic blue
screen. And they said that they had more
control
um filming over there rather than in the
actual water, you know. But but here's
the thing, they still had to simulate
the most realistic water effects. So
even though they're not in the middle of
the water, it is still really rough on
them. So that was interesting. Oh, it's
slobbering. Not sobering.
My bad. I will slobber up. Okay.
Halloween Horror Nights. Oh my gosh.
Wait, isn't that only for Japan though?
[music] Or is that also going to be in
the the US one? That'll be nice. But I
don't think I'll have time for um
Yuktober one. Thank you, Ko. Bye-bye.
And Sasa, welcome back. Oh, they do in
the US. I had no idea. Slobbering. It's
kind of like imagine your dog and
imagine you're a chew toy. You're now in
the dog's mouth as a chew toy. They are
slobbering on you.
Uh, let's see.
Oh, maybe. Oh, no, no, no. Zeta sent me
the picture cuz I think my hands are
full. I remember now. In the Star Wars
one, they had some creepy weird
monsters.
Uh, what was the one that she sent me?
It looked kind of realistic, like a
skin.
Um, where is she? See, this one.
Yeah, it looked like a a weird cockroach
with some fur. It It's kind of bipedal,
too. Bipedal. It It was kind of like
naked.
And it's mostly skin. It's mostly
hairless except for around the neck.
Yeah. I don't know what it was. I was
kind of tempted to buy it though because
it was kind of ugly.
Yeah. You don't know what it is? It's
brown. It has like a black beak and it
has weird long ears that pivot sideways.
Hi Oscar. Thank you for the SC. It have
a long and interesting history. Oh, I
had no idea. Job at the hut. Maybe a
rancer. Let me Google it.
No, but I think they were selling that
though. And not a rancer. It was a
little bit tinier. It looked like a bug.
Star Wars. Maybe uh Jaba henchman.
Let me look. Oh, it's uh Salacious
Beerrumb.
Is that Is that a thing? Yeah, whatever
it is. It says in the Google image
salacious beer crumb. I was kind of
tempted to buy it because it's so
freaky. I thought it would be a puppet.
It's ugly.
I don't know what it is, but it's ugly.
but in like I would collect this sort of
way, but I decided against it because
you actually have to plug it in. I
didn't really want to plug that in, you
know? It's like kind of a waste of
space. I think it's meant to be a It's
supposed to have a talking function.
Honda's little bird thingy. I think so.
Yeah. Did I see a baby Yoda? I saw it
for something, but I can't remember what
it was. I think it was only in like a
video form during the waiting time.
Uh, let's see.
Oh, yeah. In Universal Studios, they
also had uh like a little Harry Potter
area or whatever. It was kind of small,
but I stopped by there to eat some of
the food. The food was actually really
good. I was very pleasantly surprised.
For the food,
I don't know how much I had, but the
food in the Universal Studios was kind
of more enjoyable for me compared to the
Disney one. Disney one was kind of just
like it was okay. I like their gumbo
thinking about it and their beignette,
but everything else is kind of like me.
Butterbeer. I did try the butterbeer.
The butterbeer was pretty good. I did
enjoy it even though it was a little It
had a little bit of an after taste or
some sort of shock to it. Wasn't it
slightly carbonated? Maybe that's why I
was a little hesitant on it. But it was
it was really good. I don't even know
what the freak it is, but I liked it.
And you can get like a little steel mug
there, too. But for there, I had the
shepherd's pie. And I tried to be
healthy, guys. I ate a salad. The salad
was acceptable, but the pie was really
great. And then there's this dude just
pose in front of a train. I don't know
who he is. I think he's just a random
conductor. Anyway, I took a picture of
him cuz why not?
It's Butterscotch. Oh,
the Terminator one. Oh, they had a
Terminator one.
Minions. Hey, I wrote the Minions.
You're so right though. The minion
destroy was kind of like wasn't it
wasn't the best in my opinion. Noan,
welcome back. I hope you're doing well.
It's been a while since I've seen you, I
think.
Here, let me skip around first.
So, in I only rode one ride here,
though, cuz I did not want to wait. The
other one was a little bit hectic. It
was a little bit more crazier, and you
had to leave your stuff behind. You had
to get a locker for it, which isn't so
bad, but it's kind of a pain. So, I went
to the one that had a little bit of a VR
experience. First off, it's one of the
most popular rides. So, you should
probably get here as fast as possible.
And it's kind of interesting the way
they run things. Basically, there's no
time to like stop and sit. They're going
to have a sort of conveyor belt moving
one way and the ride moving the other.
You're going to have to just quickly get
in as fast as you can.
So, that was a thing. And they decked
out the waiting experience. So once
you're there, basically you're expected
to sort of uh fly above things. You're
going to be midair, which was the really
cool part. And then I believe um Harry
just shows up on a broom
flying around. [laughter]
I don't know why, but then suddenly
dragon shows up. A dragon shows up and
is like chasing him. I don't even know
why we were in there. Were we like
chasing the ball or something? That
could be the only explanation. I don't
know who I ever been air. I never
watched much of this. So, dragon shows
up, throws fire at you. Uh, you're taken
to a new location. Um, the roof is
suddenly on fire. More dragons shows up.
I think they're animatronics. That was
really cool. I'm still watching the
footage. Uh, you're going to a spider
forest. I don't know why you're in the
forest, but you're freaking stuck in
there. You're in the forest. Giant
spiders. lots of cobwebs.
Um, Hermione shows up, probably tells
you to get the freak out, and she says
like, "I'll hold them off." And she does
nothing.
Still floating around. Oh, and this is
the really cool part because you're in
pitch black darkness except for a few
light sources. Um, they try to jump
scare you with a giant spider like right
in front of your face and it's not 2D.
It's like an actual 3D thing. And then I
think they try to show those like little
phantom things, whatever those are.
really neat though. It It's really fun.
I loved it. Thank you, Infamous and
Mystic. Did I conduct myself? No. Oh,
and then all of a sudden after the
forest, you're back on like chasing the
ball. Chasing a flying ball in like an
arena and I think that one dude. H
shoot. What's his face? The rival of
Harry Potter. Freak. Malfoy. Malfoy
shows up, does nothing.
You're still chasing the stupid ball for
no reason. Oh, and then then the phantom
show up and they're trying to take the
ball from Harry Potter, I think. I don't
know why. I have absolutely no idea why.
I think they just started to suddenly
attack everyone and then you go back
into some spooky section and then
there's more phantoms showing up. Really
cool, by the way. Like they were they
were realistic, you know.
Um, what else?
some skeleton shows up, but that one's
holographic.
And then pitch black darkness for who
knows how long.
Um, and then I I'm pretty sure it ends
at some point. [laughter]
And they're like, "You did it. You did
it. You defeated evil
at the end." And there's like a whole
group photo of like all the the wizards
and whatever. And it's like, okay. Um,
there was there was some merch there
that I thought was really cute.
I think it's one of the other series
though. It looked like something from
Monster Hunter. It was a pink puff ball
that looked kind of like a flamingo, and
I was really tempted to buy it, even
though I had no idea what it was. I just
thought it was super cute, so I liked
it.
Uh, what else is there? I did not do the
Fast and Furious ride.
I didn't I don't even know what that's
about. I I think I was confusing it with
like the Fantastic 4.
>> [laughter and crying]
>> Is it a moon calf? Let me look.
Uh, let's see.
Moon calf. Moon calfe.
No, I don't think it was a moon calf.
But they I think they did sell that. No,
it was something else. It was more pink.
It was pink and round. Um,
pink round animal.
Oh, it's a pygmy puff. It was so cute.
Are they evil? I don't know what they
are, but they're just like they're
really adorable. I liked it, but I
decided against it. Yeah, it's a Pikmi
Puff, whatever the freak that is. So,
besides that, there was also I think the
pets region or some sort of display of
Paris.
Um, this is also the area that has like
something called Mulan Rouge and they
had a water park. Did anyone teach me
new Japanese? I forgot my
You are welcome to teach me Japanese.
Kevin, welcome back.
Any of the references? That's me every
day. [laughter]
Fast and Furious. No, sorry. Alina Mario
Kart.
Uh, anyway, there's this section where
there is a minions and monsters. It was
so cute. I like it. I don't even watch
Minions. I watched one movie. I And then
like there's a guy named Gru. He has
children adopted. I just I think the
minions are really cool though. Oh. Oh,
there was this there was this thing I
wanted. It was like um a a unicorn
stuffed animal and a backpack. It looks
so derpy. I loved it. I think it's part
of the Groom movie, which I think is
called Minions, maybe. Or Minions is
part of the Groom movie. I have no idea.
But it was so funny, but I was like,
"Oh, should I or should I not?" So, I
held off on it for now.
And then eventually, I couldn't resist
the urge. Um, so there's some games that
had the unicorn there and if you
defeated like four people, you can
select the top prize or you could just
select the lesser prizes, you know. Um,
I was really I'm kind of I'm clearly low
low
confidants though. I looked at the
people that were playing. I was like,
"Oh, if I play with them and I win, I
could get something, but if I lose, I
get nothing." And then I I was debating
on like maybe maybe I should defeat the
children so I could get my goods. But
it's like, you know, but what if the
children beat me? I would look really
pathetic.
But eventually
eventually I couldn't stand anymore. I
went against adults, guys. It was one v
one v3. We know one out of four people.
I I won. I won. And instead of getting
the unicorn, I got like the king minion,
though. [laughter]
It's like, well, this is a limited
prize. To get this, you have to defeat
four people, and this is the max prize,
so I went with it. So, I took the the
biggest, hardest to get plush after
defeating all the strangers. And then I
went into their merch store. Now, this
is not the same merchandise they have
it. So, I did get a limited edition
thing. Um, but they were selling the
unicorn as a backpack, so I decided to
get that one instead.
Have I seen her? I have not seen her.
Shadikon, maybe she's on the other side
of the hot stream because she has a
penis. So, no, I have not seen her.
I like it though. I don't know when I'll
ever use it, but I liked it. And then I
went to the actual minions ride. It was
just kind of like a nice little
wholesome story. Basically, they it was
their anniversary of adoption and they
wanted to give him a present and then
they lost the present and they're just
trying to help him get it back. It was
like really cool though, but the wait is
so long. It's just so insane how long of
a thing it is. So, that was the thing.
Oh, and then this one I had no idea
about, but apparently
apparently Scooby-Doo is part of
Universal Studios
and I had no idea. And then and then
Scooby was there and I'm like, Scooby,
Scooby, hugged me. [laughter]
So, he hugged me. I got a hug from
Scooby, guys. He hugged me and and then
Shaggy was talking and Belma was so like
nice to me. She was like, "You're so
polite and sweet." And I told Scooby,
like, "Please hug me. I don't get any
from my parents."
Hi, Crush. Thank you. And thanks for the
tweets, by the way. I saw you make some.
Thank you. Good luck with your work.
Shaggy was telling some story. He
actually really looked good as Shaggy.
I'll be honest. It's probably like glued
on to him, but he he made for a good
Shaggy. I feel like I feel like
literally anyone
could probably kill you off a [music]
shaggy as long as you're tall and
starving. [laughter]
Thank you, Vel. Yay.
And then besides besides that, um they
also had Nintendo Land. I didn't know it
was part of it either. Um I had the
pretzel, some sort of fire pretzel. They
also had Cowzones and they had some
limited edition stuff. And they also had
the Nintendo like restaurant.
So in case you want to know, they also
had a Kung Fu Panda sort of like mini
movie experience. They put you in seats,
but the only issue is like it really is
just a personal viewing. It doesn't
really feel like a ride. So I thought it
was kind of like meh. Like it was a cool
premise. They definitely tried to
utilize utilize the stage for it, but at
that point they should have just used it
for long movies rather than Yeah, this
is a ride experience cuz it's not.
I didn't get to do the mummy ride. That
was kind of sad, but it was so hectic
already. I did do the trans Oh my gosh,
guys. I'm going to be so honest. The
Transformers ride was really good. Like
my god, it was such an excruciating
weight, though. It was so so long. But
but what's his face? Optimus Prime. I I
think he's kind of hot.
I don't know. Something about he
Something about the way he commands is
just sort of attractive for a hunk of
metal. Yeah.
I think I confused him for the other
dude though. Metatron. I was like, I
don't know. But Optimus Prime, he's so
good. He's at the prime of his life. So,
if you are to go to Universal Studios,
really quite a shame I didn't go to the
Jurassic one and the Mummy, but it was
like late. Um, go to the at least one of
the Harry Potter ones, the VR experience
in my opinion. And definitely
Transformers. That was so good. And then
the rest. Um, if you can make it, do it.
Ah, my phone.
I dropped it in the water. Oopsies.
Let me let me grab it with my with my
oozing body.
Did they have a suit actor? I don't
think so. I don't remember seeing it.
Oh yeah,
she's Liz. What do you mean?
My Mecca arc. She is hot though. You
know, you had an anime for Transformers.
He had an anime for it and then they had
the movie. Actually, I don't even know
why it became popular. Was it because of
the anime? It's like it's time to roll
out. Oh, I'll roll out for you, Optimus
Prime.
Why do you have your phone? So I could
take loving pictures of you, Macheter.
Um, for Nintendo Land, they basically
had you go enter the castle as the
entrance. It was kind of small. It was
really good though, but it was kind of
small. Um, ridewise, unless I missed
something. It's just mostly a photo op
area.
They they had one ride. It was a Mario
Kart Bowser's challenge. It was so long
as well. I mean, I I also have a
fondness for Bowser now. I will admit
Bowser's hilarious cuz he's like the
biggest but funniest hater. If you go
into his castle, they decked it out with
his personality. And by that, I mean if
you go in, let me let me look for a
picture.
He had books. And the books were sort of
like references to what he likes, which
I thought was kind of cute.
Um,
he had
dental hygiene for chain chomps, shy guy
behind the mask, better golf for heavy
hitters,
uh, the subtle art of breathing fire, a
practical guide to world domination,
the double dash years. Like a lot of the
books had references to things he likes
or things he was trying to do.
It also kind of showed you like what his
factory looked like. And he kind of has
a throne room that has Princess Peach on
the throne, like a little portrait of
her. And she's also plastered on the
wall. So, he's dedicated. Bowser is a
real romantic guy, guys. He reads, he
leads an army. I'm going to be so
honest. If I was Peach, I would probably
just get with Bowser at this point.
Like, is it really world domination if
the only focus he has is getting Peach?
Like, come on, guys.
He doesn't even do anything. He gets her
and does what? They have tea parties.
Like come on. If Peach really wanted
Mario and she clearly does not, she
would have gone with him by now, guys.
They have a polycule.
But like he's he's such a swave guy.
He's swave.
He's like the biggest hater, too. But
he's trying to constantly improve on his
metric of hatred.
Like he's not just a hater. He actually
does something about it, guys. He runs a
factory. And there's even a picture of
how much he makes a day. He had a
factory of like he makes 20 bomb bombs a
day or 50. He has like um the bullet
bills. This is how much they make. And
then they lead to the Mario Kart ride.
Actually, I recommend that one, too. Go
to the Mario Kart ride as early as you
can. Basically, what happens is that
they launch you into a cart. They gave
you some sort of VR glasses, but you
take it, you kind of take it with you on
the ride. They have some sort of like
magnetic class and you just put the
glasses on there and it becomes an AR
experience. So, you just have to touch
some button on the cart and you can
launch shells. You can control like
where you are. Naturally, you have to
work with your group though. So, if your
group is like trying to go left but you
go right, it's kind of [music] gonna
fight back a little.
So go there if you can. Weightwise, not
worth it, but really good ride.
And that was about it cuz I think after
all of that stuff, I was freaking tired.
Oh, there was an ET merch. That's right.
ET is so ugly. [laughter]
ET is so ugly, but I was tempted to buy
the ET hat because it was so like Oh my
god. Let me go find it. if I can. Guys,
the ET hat is atrociously funny. ET hat
cap.
It's like, oh my god,
it's just so hideous.
Oh, you can get on eBay. 60 bucks.
Okay, maybe here.
Uh, I don't want anything tracking, so
maybe if I do this one,
I'm going to assume that works. Yeah.
Ooh.
All right. Here. This This is what the
hat looked like, by the way. I was kind
of tempted to get it,
not going to lie,
because it'd be so funny wearing it
around and looking kind of pathetic.
It is so hideous. He needs to get
moisturized.
But I showed it to um Watame Senpai. I
showed it to you. I was like, "Hey." She
was like, "Hey,
good job with work today, Senko." And
Remalins. Oh, I hope you sleep well.
So that's what it it is hideous. I know.
It's so ugly. And then at the Jurassic
section, they had popcorn buckets. They
had popcorn buckets of the dinosaurs and
the shark. And I was really tempted to
get it, but realistically speaking, it
doesn't carry that much popcorn. So, I
feel like the Jaws bottle might be worth
it though. But it's also kind of a pain
because you just have that gigantic
thing and what? Just a tiny tiny water
bottle. It's not very portable. So, I
decided against it. It's like, no, I'll
just take a picture. Weirdo. Thanks for
dropping by. Have a good sleep. Oo, some
of you guys sleep early. Someone's
healthy. Oh, then they had for some
reason they had Hello Kitty, but she's
kind of collabing with other brands.
There was a Hello Kitty Chucky edition,
which was fascinating.
And yeah, I think that's pretty much it.
I did go ahead and buy a Scooby-Doo
plush, though. [music]
And I was so happy I managed to stuff it
in the luggage. And I also got some
gifties for the girls, and they were
pretty happy about it. I'll let them
talk about it if they ever choose to
though.
Um, and then
on the final day before we all headed
out, naturally, [music] we had like
dinner and stuff. Um, it was a really
nice place. I liked it. I had some sort
of Is it a mocktail? Is that what it's
called? I don't know. I went whatever
was non-alcoholic cuz they don't usually
taste good.
And I ate a salad, guys. I ate another
salad.
Alli, welcome back. inspire cash grabs
is Mac and me. I've never seen that
either. Bunker, thank you for the SC.
Yeah, they had this really nice place.
Uh I won't go into too much detail just
in case they want to go back there,
though.
Oh, yeah. This one. I had I saw this one
thing. I Where did I take a picture of
this from? Oh, it's probably during the
museum. For some reason, on the ground
it said, "God, are you afraid of
Godzilla?" And I was like, "What?"
I I was trying to go into a museum
spree, but I was so tired. So, I was
only able to go to one. Um, it is closed
now. So, even if I tell you to go, it is
too late. But there is a tarpit museum.
For those who don't know what that is,
imagine black sludge. Imagine you
falling into black sludge. You are now
most likely well preserved
if you have fallen in a good distance
underneath. Yeah, the tar pit because we
played LA Noir before and I was kind of
curious all about it. It was kind of a
small museum, I will admit. They had
fossils and some displays and info about
extinct creatures. You could sort of
feel stuff out and there's like fencing
areas where I believe there's still some
tars over there,
but I did not want to stay outside. So,
so yeah, it was real. Unfortunately,
they are now closing for 2 years. So,
I'm pretty sure that a bunch of people
came before I could close. They're
renovating. I think they're moving out
the items they have to make space for
new ones and whatnot. Will they all have
new tar? I'm not sure.
So, yeah, that was pretty much it. two
years exactly. It's a really long time.
I wanted to buy some sort of rock
collection from there because they had a
sort of collector's thing. Not that it's
exclusive, but it was a is it called a
STEM kit? I don't know. Some sort of
learning thing. I wanted to do a hand
cam for it, but my luggage was too full
cuz I had a gigantic unicorn plush. I
had Scooby-Doo. I had a little minion.
Well, he wasn't little though. He was a
big minion. He was humongous.
And I also tried out um I went to the
Nintendo restaurant.
What did I have there? By the time I
came there, some of the more niche foods
were kind of out though. But the food
was good. I tried a dessert. It was
nice. Sort of like tiramisuesque.
And they had a three tiered small cake.
Uh they let you buy a little mushroom
bowl which was nice. The restaurant was
kind of busy though.
You kind of have to if you can try to do
like a mobile queue, get reservations of
some kind if possible cuz otherwise it's
going to be a pain.
And that's pretty much it. Yeah, the
toad cafe. Yeah, it was cute. So,
basically inside it's kind of wooden
theme. I feel like I'm in a tree. So
around you have little fake windows and
they have display screens of toads doing
toad things and they're just like making
food or just walking around a park and
occasionally there would be a fake
thunderstorm
and then the the screen or the lights in
the room would dim.
So yeah, good luck with work, Stephen.
It was fun. I liked it. Yeah. Did I eat
pizza? I ate it with Zeta. and Kobo. And
then we also did have pizza for catering
for the concert stuff, but I didn't
finish that though.
Yeah, go is really nice. He gave us some
like treats. I kind of wish I stole
some.
Kind of wish I stuffed it in my bag cuz
I'm pretty sure those are going to get
dumped out. But they had some very uh
nice chocolate treats and there's like
the ramen. They did not give me the
sandwich I wanted though, which is the
thing. But it's like it's okay. It's
like I wish you kind of gave it to me. I
don't know what happened, but whatever.
I'm just going to take these cookies and
then not eat them.
Yeah. Also dropped by as you saw cuz
Kiara already took a picture of him
wearing a shirt. It's spectacular. I'm
glad you liked it. You met some prehat.
I'm glad, Sammy. I'm glad you had a fun
time.
Yeah, I think like concerts and whatnot
are probably the best time to meet
people if possible.
I don't know how, but but it's possible.
No, he would not mind. He He absolutely
would be okay with it because like once
these are done and open, no one else can
have them. I'm pretty sure he just gets
tossed. So that's why he might as well
just take them. I didn't have space
though. That's the issue.
My favorite thing I ate during the trip.
Trying to remember.
I like the Mickey beignettes, but they
didn't kind of get beets anywhere and
they're just shaped like that. The gumbo
was pretty good. Even the the tavern
food, the shepherd's pie was kind of
amazing. It was just soft and like
flaky,
you know. Whatever about the salad, but
yeah, I think I think a lot of the food
was pretty good. Oh, actually I did have
Mexican food. Yeah, I did have some some
authentic. I think they're authentic. I
actually cannot confirm, but I'm going
to assume so because they're not Taco
Bell. I had some really good food. Very
spicy.
U I feel like the thing with me and
Mexican food though, now that I've come
to appreciate them, I don't really like
it when they're in the tortilla.
I feel like the tortilla is like a fake
hot dog, if that makes sense. It's
really to buy time. What I want is the
meats, the gritty bitty meats. I want
them hot. I want it steamy. I want it
like with lots of sauce. If I add that
to the the sort of shell, that's kind of
taking away the time to enjoy my meat.
Wait, funnily enough, now that I think
about it, when we were hanging out for
Disney,
um,
Kobo and Zeta ordered like a some sort
of burger or some breakfast sandwich,
they didn't eat the bread, guys. They
didn't eat the bread. They did. They
just went straight for it. The sandwich
was actually really good. I did enjoy
it. It's also kind of heavy. I really
like the uh the chocolate banana. I
should buy chocolate bananas. I have
come to appreciate the beauty that is a
chocolate banana in the same way I have
come to find beauty in your skin as I
respectfully slobber up and moisturize
you with my body.
Thanks to Abby for for making this by
the way. Expect some maybe another snail
lori stream. The fly welcome. Let me get
some water.
Drinking water. Oh, I'm going to drink
the water off your skin.
This water tastes weird. Tastes like
water.
You know, out of everyone in this
hotring,
you're the quietest. I like that about
you.
Oh.
You also have such nice nice skin
texture. Makes me just want to rub up
against it and glisten with my with my
mucus. Girly,
did you did you know that we might have
a snails may have 14,000 teeth? And just
to just so you know, I'd use every
single one just for you, just so I can
suckle that skin.
>> [laughter]
>> Guys, it's okay. I'm a snail. I can get
away with this.
Oh, and I'm also I happen to be made out
of mostly water. So, us being in the
water together, we match pretty well,
darling.
What? Snails are cool. There was
actually a girl with a snail bag. I
remember seeing her and I tapped her in
your arm saying like, "I love your bag.
It's so cool."
That's outstanding. I'm really glad. I'm
really glad. I'm actually very proud of
how The Devil Rises um how do you say
it? Went. Funnily enough, when Mory said
like, "I feel something rising." I kept
thinking of the shield hero.
Instead of saying like, you know, I kept
thinking of the devil. I just kept
thinking of something else. I like Okay.
Which makes sense because if you didn't
know what the song was called, like you
would think something else.
Why am I moving constantly? Oh, it's
probably because the fan's moving it.
Yeah, I guess. Yeah, it's the fan. I'll
keep it here.
There you go. It's not as bad now.
You're getting a new se Wait, there's a
new season.
Is there
a soft summer breeze that caresses your
skin? Even though here it clearly looks
like it's autumn. This is season five.
I'm not even watching it anymore. We
already know how most isekai ends. They
become a god and they make a clone of
themselves and a clone stays in one
spot. Another clone stays in the
original spot and they sent to godhood.
Come on.
Come on, guys. Most isekai end like
that. There's always going to be a clone
or some sort of herum or whatever.
Let me look at my calendar. I actually
do want to play more Street Fighter at
some point. I was actually really
tempted to just start it.
We need to do Street Fighter story mode.
And then for
for Friday, we have Mega Chameleon that
we'll try. It's just reserve for the
novel Knights first dibs. And don't
forget your your Street Fighter 1994.
You can get on Amazon. When I open up
the stream room, I'll also link to it
just so you don't like mistake it. And
now we're watching a I believe Attack on
Titan is getting a new game. I remember
playing some smaller ones. I didn't even
know they were on three. I'm actually
very surprised about it, but I'm
interested to see what it's about. I
don't think it's going to be a very long
stream for that one. So, just hang out
with me and we'll see what's happening.
And next week, next week is a lot of
collabs
free. Yeah. Um, I will be doing a hand
cam stream
and then we're going to do Should I be
moving that way? I need to think about
that one.
I might move that one. No. No. But but
these are kind of close to each other
and they're both No, this one should be
fine. It's kind of talking over it.
We're going to have another indie game
showcase. So, if you enjoyed the last
one I hosted, the one that was inkwell
sponsored by me,
um, please [music] keep an eye out on
the indie game showcase for this one as
well.
Yeah, Crimson, welcome back. And Yokugo,
thanks for upgrading. Katarina, thanks
for the SC. You met some cosplayers.
[music]
You like the snails? Yay.
Oh, yeah.
Um, probably no guest because I just
think it's kind of hard to have a guest.
[music] And then you're on a timer for
things. We'll see. I mean, I still have
a lot of games to go over. I believe
there's maybe 35 games I'm going over
for this one. And I have vetted them.
So, it should be some really neat
months. And hopefully you can find
something you do like. Happy birthday,
Sorus. I hope you have a great birthday
today.
You convince her kid that you you live
in a blue sub in Canada. You don't have
to convince them. It's true.
What do you mean it's true?
Yeah. Just like being a little snail.
You did you know that I have a voice
pack? I have I have a voice pack, guys.
Did you Did you Did you know I have a
voice pack? If you ever want a little
bit of snailor action, you should get my
voice pack where you are in a hotring.
Yes. Yes. I'm actually really excited.
There's some future voice packs already
that I'm very proud of how it turned out
or it's going to turn out, whichever
word words, man. But I'm very proud of
it. You should definitely get one of the
voice packs that I will promote in the
future, some months from now. Very proud
of it. I get to see a little bit of
something of you. Whoopee. And then
there's another one that I've actually
signed. Oh my gosh. How much did I sign
up for? Well, only those. I only signed
up for ones I have a really good idea
for. Well, if you get all of them, I
think some of them like for How many
voice packs did I do? I have no idea.
I'm proud of this one, though. Which
ones am I really proud of? I was really
proud of the the seat beside mine.
I was really happy with that. How uh
with how it turned out as well
for the future one.
I'm really proud of how this one turned
out as well. Um, it's kind of like an
anniversary one. Not related to advent,
it's just more of like it's been a while
since I've been in here.
And then in a different one,
I'm curious how that's going to go and I
kind of want to make a stream out of it.
It's sort of similar to this where I
just take on the form of the voice pack
character.
You talk about novela at your school.
Nice. That sounds wonderful. Hello,
Joker. Thanks for dropping by. The
earbuds with your voice sold out at AX.
Oh, did everyone sold out? We're a
group, aren't we?
Yeah. I don't know how the earbuds were.
I'm pretty sure they go as a group. The
Aviates. Yeah. Or aviots. Ah, excuse
them. I need to go pace after this. I'm
trying to get back into my my pacing,
which has been working out pretty well,
actually. Me. Thanks. As long as I focus
on my health. You might not
cipher. Welcome.
Yeah, I'm getting back to my steppies.
I'm also kind of well, temporarily. You
don't know how long this will last. But
after I came back from LA, I fell asleep
at like 8:00 p.m. and then I woke up
like really early.
A little bit too early. I feel like my
problem is I just I cannot stay asleep.
Even if I go to bed at a good time,
which is like, thank God, staying asleep
and leaving bed are kind of the two
difficult things.
I know. 8:00 p.m. crazy. Do I have jet
lag? I don't think so. I think it's just
fatigue. My body was definitely catching
up on sleep. It was definitely very
tired along the No, my body's just like
this. It just it just be. Funny enough,
I accidentally wore one of my like my
Apple watches while sleeping and then it
told me like, "You had a difficult time
sleeping."
I was like, "Yeah, thanks. Thanks for
telling me." I wasn't supposed to marry
you as I fell asleep, but I did somehow.
It's like, okay, thank you.
Really, really good thing to know.
It's like, okay. Yep.
Your watch roast you a lot, too. O, the
apple knows now.
Uh, what else?
Nothing else in my opinion. I think I
just have to get back into the scope of
things. Um, oh, I'm very happy that the
two songs I've been waiting for so long
and they're almost done.
So, there is going to be a future song
cover that will be releasing
within the next few months.
No, probably within I want to say within
this or next month, actually. So, I'm
very very happy with that. like, yippee.
We just got to do some polish and then
another song. Um,
oh shoot, when do I have to do that one?
Oh, I don't know. But most I think it's
basically done. And then I have a cover
I did with someone else that'll be on
their channel that I'm also very like
happy to participate in. And then
I have two songs that I'm hoping to
sing. I'm just trying to get like some
extra bits like harmonies on one of them
now that I decided about it because I've
done the lyrics for a long time. I just
have not got into it. And then the other
one I had to make the instrumental cuz I
got to lower the pitch. But yeah, it's
going to be interesting. And then if I
have another song I really want to do, I
shall
think about it. Yeah, I think I'm
already commissioning the the
instrumental, so I really do need to get
that one done. Yay! Thank you, Lamar.
Thanks for dropping mine. Thanks for the
SC. No worries. Brawl as well. And a
crone
w.
I've been doing so much, have I? It's
mostly been just like work trips and
[music] being busy for work, though.
Hello,
JR E. I don't know how to say your name.
It made you cry. A, they're there. I
miss Hatchima. I want to invite her for
something. I think like when I
eventually take my my really long work
trip slash um mental health break. I'll
still be streaming though. It's just
going to be in Japan. That's the only
thing. I'll probably try to get some
vlog footage and invite people for them.
I don't want it to be too hectic. So, I
have to really decide who to bring for
which thing. So, that's going to be my
my goals, I think. So this is like I
might as well I'm going to be there for
a while so I can be under supervision so
people make sure I eat and stuff.
So I do want to invite her for
something.
I've been a really busy snail Bella. I
feel like because I've been doing other
things so I haven't actually had time to
focus on like as much as I want to on
certain things. Like we used to have
community events and whatnot.
It's probably it's mostly a health issue
probably. Oh I'm sorry to hear that
miso. They're there. Well, let's go have
lots of fun. Uh, let me look at my
schedule. I will tell you now, I am
going to play Resident I will be playing
Resident Evil 5
next week, but I will have to figure out
the scheduling for that since that one's
a really long game. And we'll probably
only do like three hour sessions [music]
or so depending on things.
And then I have
um
two streams. This one's a shorter game.
I'm going to try asking perms for her
thinking about it cuz she she has not
gotten perms. I'm just going to ask
since I have it. But I'm going to be
playing Little Hope uh with
with someone and we'll kick his ass.
We will kick his ass.
You liked it? Thank you, troll. Yippee.
Your brain chemistry. I should do
something with more and more. Yeah,
she'll be busy though, isn't she? I'll
ask her. I'll think about it.
Lil Hope is awful. I'm going to feel so
bad cuz I genuinely cannot stand people
dying on my watch.
I I'm going to feel bad about it. At
least Resident Evil, you can you just
have each other to protect, right? And
like the one person you can't just
prevent uh deathwise, the chopper
person. You can never protect chopper
people in Resident Evil.
Uh over Chris in Resident Evil 5. A
That's okay. That's okay. Not everyone
can punch boulders. He's so badass
though.
You don't trust this guy to keep it
what? No.
I Well, I'm going to try and protect
everyone. I just can't wait to bicker.
And then for Resident Evil 5, I'm really
curious how she's going to play.
I'm not very
Can I Can I just ask you? Don't Don't
mention her name. Okay. How good is How
How good is Zeta with shooters?
Just cur How can Do you think it'll be
okay? [laughter]
Do you think she's good with She can
shoot like enough to live. She's right.
She's right. She's pretty decent. Okay.
I'm just not the worst. Okay. I'm good
hands. [laughter]
[gasps] She plays Apex. Okay.
As long as she can live because I think
that game sometimes requires you to
separate, doesn't it? And that's like
the scary part.
[crying]
All right. All right. I'm I I'm looking
forward to it with my girly.
Apex isn't a standard. I don't know
anything about Apex, guys. I think I'm
decent, though. I am coming to terms
with the fact that I am a decent gamer.
Did I forget Pippy?
For what?
The pig
pippy lean. Welcome back, Sana. Welcome.
Who's that? Is that a chopper? I don't
know. My characters in Resident Evil. I
hope you know that. A very good gamer.
Thank you. Um, I do want to play more
Dark Souls. I might actually I'm above
average. I I think so, too. I I
definitely think I might be above
average.
I pick things up very quickly. I just
don't like the stress about it. I don't
want people expecting things, guys.
Is it from Poppy? Poppy? Ah, you mean
Poppy's Playtime? I'm going to hold off
on that cuz I don't want to stress out.
The final boss fight for episode 3 was a
lot. Plus, the thing with Poppy's
Playtime is that they still don't have
episode 6. So, I'm like kind of halfway
through there, but I'm going to forget
everything regardless. So, I think we
can kind of take our time on that. But,
I kind of want to do Dark Souls 3I.
We're going to do co-op. I will not
finish these games without co-op. Like,
that's kind of my issue with Wukong. I
really love Blackth Wukong. That was a
fun game. I just cannot be asked to find
pillars. I can't be asked to find
pillars. I really don't want to keep
dying just to redo everything in terms
of like, oh, got to do this puzzle now.
Uh, the Road to Empress game. Yeah, I
finally got the trailer. I need to see
if who I can invite for it, though.
Um, I'll think about that, but if have
the final trailer, and I'm pretty sure
we actually have perms for the sequel
now, or at least we're trying to get it,
but I think we have it. I think he was
on top of things.
Yeah, but right now I have my collabs
for next week and a hand cam stream and
the indie game showcase
and then things are kind of leading up
to the debut stuff. I'm not going to do
anything too fancy, just the usual
um usual shior tier.
Uh Kiz, I debated on it. It's mostly
like a timing thing cuz I usually do it
at night. We'll see. We'll see. We'll
think about it.
I'll see.
How's Emma doing? I don't know. Probably
still pregnant. I think he's okay.
Yeah, I think he's just been busy doing
manager stuff. But the the other
manager, Caps, she's pretty good. I like
her. She's very nice.
She's very on top of things, too. It's
very interesting.
I think uh I'll just call staff nyakuza
just to do I think I have an idea for
the nyakuza too but I'm going to keep it
a secret. I'm going to keep it in my
pouch. I'm going to keep it in my oil
glands. My snail muc mucosa.
Let me let me
No. No. Yeah. Absolutely. He is
definitely pregnant. I believe he is
having
quadruplets.
He's been busy birthing each one one by
one. Absolutely.
Um Brian, welcome back. Thank you for
the SC. I'm glad you had a great time.
And Chisu, yeah, I also had um this one
plan. It's just I need to think about
the execution of it. So, I don't know if
you guys knew, but for those who don't
know for Fest, we actually have a book,
the Inqua Chronicles. Everything that
was made by members, we compiled all of
it. So stories written by members aren't
commissioned for it. We didn't I didn't
think to do this before. So it's kind of
like something that was done
retroactively. Is that the term? So it
was something like we have all the data.
Let's go back and find all of it. And
then the book came to be. Now my future
idea is I think we should focus on Chibi
Bella since the third year is almost
upon us and now we will be going into
the fourth year. crazy thinking about
it. Um, we should probably try to focus
on some sort of cute chibiella
mysteries. So, I need to think about the
execution of it. And if you're not too
confident on writing, I think maybe just
brainstorming like sort of key words and
we'll go do that.
Yeah. No, I think that would be a really
great idea. Something like urban myth
dissolution center.
And then I think I would like to make
that into a book as well. Naturally, I
don't think they'll be sold.
Maybe. No, I don't I don't know. We'll
see. Cuz the book was published on my
end anyway rather than like the company
end. So, we'll see. It depends on what I
am able to do. I think about it. But
yeah, it'll be a fun project. Then I
also had some ideas. It's just
execution. So, I I probably have to make
more time for like [music] behind the
scenes work just to do things. And I
need to make my script or something.
I went to the museum. I think they were
expecting it to be done by now, but I
did not. I did not do it. I did one
script. I need to do another script. And
I don't have enough footage for the
third one unless [music] I sneak
something in, but we'll see.
You're able to get the PDF. Yeah, that's
true. For those who don't actually that
was limited time, wasn't it? I think it
was the wallpaper's limited time and
maybe the PDF as well cuz it's posted on
a different site.
Take breaks when I can. Thank you. Yeah,
I just have to focus on my health. I
guess we all do, huh? We can't just sit
on our asses and play games all day.
Funny enough, it's just like my social
battery. But I'm glad I was able to
spend a lot of time with people. is like
spending it with Mio Mia senpai senpai
and all the girlies is just like really
nice. I'm glad that you guys also had a
fun time. I'm really really happy I was
able to deliver you the the envelopes
cuz I wasn't able to do that for fast.
That one was a little bit more like
harder to plan out. I guess it was a
little bit more hectic. I blame the
cards really. I blame the TCG cards.
In the future though,
for the future concerts, which I'm
definitely going to call Kowinky Dink. I
don't care what name it's going to be.
It's going to be Kinky Dink. Um, I want
to do something a little bit more. Oh,
yeah. Maybe I should make a story
with merch. Maybe. Maybe. Or maybe
without the merch. Yeah, maybe a story.
That would be great. Yeah.
Kinky Dink in Antarctica. No, we should
do it in Australia. And then it's going
to be outside. It's going to be an
outside concert and there's going to be
kangaroos. The kangaroos are also the
bodyguards, by the way. They're going to
check your bags, but they actually don't
know what's safe, so they might just
like fight with you for no reason at all
besides being Australian.
[laughter]
Um, but yeah, I'll think about it cuz um
it's funny, but when I was passing all
the envelopes, I was thinking like,
"Wow, this is like Slender Man except
there's 19 pages."
I hope you enjoy it. I'm sorry it's just
like the the holo not postcards, but
like you're getting use out of it more
than me. I think you guys should like it
more cuz like I don't know what to do
with those postcards. And if you already
have the merch, I'm sorry. You can
always trade with someone.
So yeah,
Yago jump scares you after you collect
all nine. He comes out of your pouch.
It's a fun activity. It is. Yeah, I
should also we should do like um another
I wonder when when was I going to do
Oops. When was I going to do that?
Should be a Twitter space.
I have no idea.
Okay, I got to do that. My goal. I'm
definitely not meeting my goal. That's
for sure. Oh, shoot. I'm going to have
to reschedule that goal.
Let's see. Any spoilers? Not that we
would know.
>> [laughter]
>> You're No, we wouldn't know anyway. You
guys are so funny. You think we'd know
things? Obviously not. We can only
assume.
But if we were to have a new Holive Gen,
they're all going to be snails, guys.
They're all going to be snails. You're
going to have one snail, maybe a
centipede. One's going to be an office
worker, making sure the centipede and
the snail don't eat each other.
Uh, let's see.
Negativo, thank you so much for the SC
and dog. You're going to treasure them.
That's good. I'm glad you're you're
enjoying it. Hol snail. Oh, that'd be
funny.
That would be funny. [music]
A praying mantis. I would love to have a
praying mantis one. I don't know if he
would. Would he ever get an insect based
one? Oh, that was a future stream idea I
had. That was going to be one of my
ideas with Mory in case like the isekai
one was a little bit too too deadly.
Okay, let me see.
I should do that. Yeah, it is fun.
Um,
okay. So, not that one. That should be
not busy. I'm going to put that my task
list for now.
Let's see. Put it on here. Um,
there you go. Now, what is this one?
They do this. Oh, I got to check this.
Okay. It kind of sucks though. Work
still piles up even if you're busy with
other work.
Reptilian themed YouTubers. I I guess it
really depends on the marketing
and like what they have.
Guess we'll see. Man, I'm seeing your
tweets. You know, I knew it. Come on.
You just because you knew it doesn't
mean you have to tweet about it. No,
it's okay. I don't mind.
Yeah, I It was going to be a snail on
stream. People who watch me would know
that. Of course they would know that.
Did you know it? Who here is a novel?
Did Did you know this would be a snail
[music] stream? Yeah.
No.
And then let me do a a blushing face.
There you go. I want to see who actually
knew it.
Come on, guys.
A lot of people seem to know it. Oh. Oh,
100%. What is up the voting? No. Oh, you
heathens. You wanted to be pervy, didn't
you? You wanted to see Shiori in a bath.
I guess I could still do that. And
funnily enough, how this works is like,
can I remove this?
Let me let me put it like this. Yeah.
Okay.
[laughter]
Don't wor Don't worry about it. Um, this
is me. Okay.
Oh, how could you not know? There you
guys go. Right there. Put it Put it like
right here.
There. Are you h I can't crop it. Okay.
Are you happy? Are you happy now? There
you go. Me and my glorious form.
Funnily enough, I there was actually
another body type I could have gotten.
Um I was torn between getting the
muscular version or I can get the female
version. But the thing is like we don't
usually we don't usually have the female
novel show up as much. So I decided, you
know, people would respect the female
body here.
So, I went with this one.
So, can I can Oh, yeah.
So, like this. This would be a little
bit better. And plus, I think this one
looks a little bit more clothed. If I
had a male version, your clothing would
be covering the bottom half. And if I
were to crop that out, it would not look
good on YouTube. But at least this one
has some sort of like sensibility, if
that makes sense. I'm an inspiration.
Thank you. And Brandon, welcome. Thank
you for becoming a novel knight. Don't
forget to check out your vlog novel
night skit monthly videos unless I mess
up in which case I will apologize.
Can I do this one? Where is this one?
Oh, it's probably elsewhere. Oh, shoot.
Um,
can I put it up here?
Oh, you kind of can.
Wait, why is one of the eyes bigger than
the other? Oh, it's cuz I'm moving like
that.
Oh, that's good. No, I like it. I think
it's fitting. Maybe. Maybe at the Oh my
god, you're like Cookie Monster.
Oh my gosh. Yeah. Oh. Oh, I'm respect.
I'm staring respectfully. Oh my gosh.
You're exactly like Cookie Monster.
Novelite monster. Nava monster. That's
so cool. I like that. These things
entertain me.
Can't believe most people thought this
would be
something else. How do you interact with
your cats in this form? Because salt and
snails aren't really a mix, right?
I'd win.
I would win. What do you mean? You think
I You think I just die from simple salt?
No way. My body was made to withstand
the ultimate amount of salt. I have the
highest sodium ever. My sodium has been
praised by the doctors. For some reason,
they are surprised by the fact that I am
still alive with high cholesterol. No,
my cholesterol is actually like decent.
I do need to work on it probably, but
it's like not bad.
But as a snail, I can withstand
anything. Did you know that cockroaches
are getting like scuba suits?
Did you guys know that?
Yeah. Yeah, we probably all got to work
on our sodium intake, man.
I just I probably got to eat more
veggies.
Yeah, cockroaches. So, scientists are
trying to see if they can send them to
the crevices in the deep. Square toe,
thank you so much for the SC. I I
welcome your toes. Um, so they're making
like little suits for cockroaches. I
don't know how they could survive the
pressure though, but that's probably the
point to see if they can. So, they're
going to be controlling them and how
like they how they go about things. So,
now not only can cockroaches most likely
survive radiation,
explosions,
uh, global climate changes, they will
probably now survive the ocean at this
rate.
They wouldn't they get crushed? That's
kind of the idea, but I'm not really
sure. That's up to the scientists. I'm
not a cockroach, thankfully.
less of the bastards on Earth. Yeah, but
they're going to be in the ocean. Next
thing you know, they're going to like
wander into your toilets. They're going
to be in your toilets, your faucet, your
shower, and they'll be they'll be
mechanized. They'll be mecha
cockroaches, guys.
God, Optimus Prime is hot. [laughter]
What is the lore of Transformers?
How did they come to be actually? Are
they like Superman? They have their own
planet of mechan mechanized cars.
Yeah. How does how does it work?
What exactly is the the war behind this?
It's just so fascinating.
It is intriguing to me.
Doesn't really stick around like that.
They came from Cyber Cybertron or was
that Cybertton?
They're aliens for Cybertron. Okay. But
why is why is um why is one guy evil?
Why is Optimus Prime good and the other
dude uh I forgot his name already.
Megatron wanted freedom.
Cybertron. Okay.
The co the comics are good. They're
comics. Megatron wanted to reform the
corrupt system. So what's Mega What's
wrong with Megatron then?
Because '8s Cyber Trren. I should watch
Transformers one. I think I watched like
I I did watch one of it. They removed a
girl. What was her Who was she again?
Mega Megan Fox. They removed her and
then they like spat on her body in a
way. If you think about it, they're
like, "Yeah, I broke up with my
girlfriend. Let's go hire this model as
my girlfriend." Was kind of what
happened.
Methods became more evil. Oh, the
Michael Bay movie. don't count. What
other Transformers are there then? I
know there's like an anime though. Anime
existed around the same time as like
what Zoids did. Zoids.
There's an an Oh, there was an animated
film. Frick. I see. There's cartoons.
Wait, there's more than one.
You love Zoids. I think I vaguely
remember seeing like trailers of it, but
one watch along. It may or may not have.
I don't care about the Doom Yi. Guys,
I'm a Yum Jooshi, not a huh,
guys. I would want the Optimus Prime for
myself.
What happens to Bumblebee? He probably
lives as on like as a [music] car.
Depends on which Transformers timeline
you wanders different ones. My gosh.
Huh.
They started in the8s. What? They're not
a 2000's thing or a 20,000 whatever
century this is. Yeah, I'm a self
inserter. You guys always confuse that.
You men, how are you how are you going
to keep confusing this? Who is uh is
Gigi? The selfinserter is me. You guys
are probably selfinstorters too, I
think.
I don't know. Selfinstors are actually
really rare apparently. Are you a
selfinserter
in terms of fiction?
Yeah. Nah.
Yeah. Selfinstorters are really rare.
Or you selfinsert some other thing.
That's not my problem though.
You wanted a grimlock. T-Rex transform.
They got you a triceratops. So you
occasionally selfinsert. That's why I
like um choose your own text adventures
a lot.
See, I told you self insertters are
rare.
I think people usually ship uh ship
instead.
>> I don't understand the mechanics of
shipping, though. I guess it's just
thinking two characters are cute. Hey,
Yi's Gigi's territory.
You always wanted to be one, but you
were never actually able to immerse
yourself like that. Oh, what would you
immerse yourself in? See, if I could, I
would actually immerse myself in lads.
If I could, I would get into love in
deep space. But I genuinely do not have
the time nor energy.
I would have been interested to see what
Balo was like though. I think like he
was going to be a a very clingy guy.
Maybe. Yeah. Lads is love in deep space
if I could. Surprisingly, I'm not. I
enjoy it the idea of it, but I genuinely
just don't grind.
I could have been in like maybe maybe I
was not
What? She's talking about you. Where are
you?
It's too big of a grind. Yeah, it it is.
That's kind of like my my thing. I don't
want to grind.
It's like if it was more of a text
adventure, I think I'd be more into it.
Yeah, she went to the lads. But wait,
Kuma, apparently you have to be like
level 60 just to get in there. It's
okay. I'll I'll become Valk, guys.
Guys, I I'll become Valk. Don't worry.
Or we could turn Liz into Valk. She's
already red. She's already halfway
there.
Just Just add like an extra DLC
attachment. Cut her hair. Put on some
wolf ears. You have Val right there.
Should I work on it? Shall I sculpt her?
To your preference, my ladies.
She's puppy co. Exactly. She's puppy
coded. Uh-huh. Exactly. Yeah.
Uh, let's see.
I would like Grand Blue. Didn't I play
that? No, I played Grand Blue Fantasy,
the other one. I haven't touched Real
Link. I have not touched Infinity Nikki.
Actually, I've not touched any games.
I've only I stopped playing Tomodachi
Life, but that's because I actually had
to go work.
God, I hope my character is still
married to my completely legal and
copyright safe character of a different
guy I like
that you already know, but I will not
mention.
Uh, let's see. Make a world that you
don't need to break cannon to work
because I make the cannon.
Oh, nah, screw cannon.
But I do like following the events of
it. But like if you're a selfinser, you
would kind of just canonically end up
changing some things.
Um, I'm Silus. You think I'd be Silus?
Really?
Honestly, Savior pisses me off though. I
gave all of Savior to Zena. [laughter]
I told her like, "Do you want this?" And
she was like, "Well, I guess
I I basically just offloaded stuff that
was gifted to me." Like, I you want it?
Yeah, you could probably gift this to
someone in Japan. [laughter]
She took one for my team. I I didn't
have the luggage space. So, I basically
just said like, "Do you have luggage
space? Do you want to like give this to
someone? I don't know who enjoys it, but
it's your problem now." So, it's like I
just gave it to her. It's like, "Okay,
she's so sweet.
She's Starscream. Isn't Starscream a
whiny guy?
You're problemat." No, that that was
what I was going to do with the
envelopes, too, if I was not allowed to
like give them out. I was going to go to
a staff member and basically say like,
"Okay, can you like [laughter] can you
take this? Figure out what to do with
it."
It's his main appeal.
I see Yoshi. Shin, thank you. Welcome.
He's always trying to backstab Megatron.
Oh, is it cuz Megatron abuses him? He's
perfect Yowi material. Oh, he always
betrays. Wait, doesn't Starcream
eventually join the good guys team?
He's Starline.
Yes and no. He doesn't. I thought he
did. Wasn't there someone who joined the
good people in the anime? Sort of. Oh,
he's always on Megatron's side. Do I
have like a Is he like reverse flash?
I'm really curious about Reverse Flash
because when I was looking at the Bowser
books, I realized, wow, he's such a good
guy in a weird way. I respect how much
he hates Mario and I ship them at the
same time. I think I think Bowser is
essentially reverse Flash.
I don't even know what happened. I just
know the concept of it is like your
biggest hater is actually also your
biggest stalker and they can't like stop
thinking about you. I think that's the
concept of it cuz Bowser is very
intelligent to be able to run his own
kingdom and he hates Mario with a
passion yet they still keep magnetizing
towards each other. So I feel like
Bowser I respect you. So now I want your
plushy. So that's how I got sold on
Bowser. Now Reverse Flash, I don't know
much about him. He's the king of petty.
That's why he's so funny. The idea of
him is funny. That's okay, Dark Spec.
Oh, good job on your first job and your
schedule stuff. I hope you enjoyed the
vod. He's the furthest possible thing
from the reverse flash. Really? What
does that mean?
You You don't think he'd like dress up
as Peach and date Mario? He wouldn't
pull like a South Park. Speaking of, I
need to put that on my schedule.
Oh, but that would get me. You know
what? Um, let me talk it out with them.
I should have people research it before
I I delve into that.
I should talk to her about Bowser,
man. Risa is just like a Wikipedia lover
like me.
She's like fanedia.
A big He was a big Flash fanboy. He
always What? He was a fanboy. Oh, and
then he turned into a hater. See, that's
the thing, though. It's like you can't
get noticed. So, like I don't know. It's
It's weird.
I think it's because you broke your
fantasy. Probably your Final Fantasy.
Speaking of the Final Fantasy, I think
they just had their final one. Guys, did
you see the news about the Final
Fantasy?
I think it's the gotcha game, right?
Yeah. I was surprised.
It's so strange.
Mhm. The last Final Fantasy. And then
apparently I think uh speaking of the
last uh the Avatar is getting a movie,
the animated movie. So I kind of want to
watch that one. It's over. A
they didn't even get their near collab
for the Gotacha.
[crying]
I was kind of surprised though. It's
canon to the FF7 remake. Oh, the Gotacha
game. I had no idea about that.
Well, we we don't mention that thing on
Twitter, but yeah. Oh, they did they did
it.
I have comments, but I shall refrain.
It's coming out early. I want to watch
it. I didn't I didn't look at the
spoilers.
I think it's interesting though,
whatever the heck's happening. Is that
also official to the the comics or is it
more of a spin-off
animated movie in theaters in the He
died. Oh my god. Why did he die by
Optimus? Was that canon
FF14? Okay, but I don't play F of 14.
That requires having like making time.
They did add it. I see. Also the
operator. I see. Oh no. That makes it
worse for people who spent on it.
It was canon. He came back to life
because I kissed him, right? [laughter]
Because Because I kissed him, right?
Gosh, that ride was so good though. He
dies a lot. Why does he keep reviving?
Did someone have a phoenix down? They
bring him back. What? They have a Dragon
Ball to bring him back to life. What's
this? What's the logic of this?
Did they really have the ability to
bring him back?
It did not go over well toys. I [music]
see.
He back. He comes back as Rodmus Prime.
Why is this Why is he Rodmus? Or is it
Roeeus?
He's the chosen. Oh, so he comes back
like um three days after death. Is that
what he is like that? Okay. I didn't
want to say the name just in case. That
is not what happens. He does not become
Rodmus. Rodmus is someone else. Who's
Rodmus?
Huh?
A mechanic came to repair him. Okay.
They were scarred [music] by his death
in the man. These kids from the 80s are
weaklings. [laughter]
I'm so sorry. H you you were traumatized
with him dying like that. Come on. Come
on. No wonder people are getting babyed
over time.
Sorry8s kids. Were you traumatized by
the little death of Optimus Prime? Oh,
boohoo.
[laughter]
It was a kid show. Look, man. When I was
a toddler, my mom let me watch scary
horrible movies. Okay. She even helped
me collect them. She said like I was
fascinated by them.
Boo freaking who? Oh no. Octopus Prime
died in my kid show. [laughter]
She raised me a while. Oh yeah, she also
dropped me probably.
'88s novel leads and shambles. No, you
can be a good 80s novel lead still. That
just depends on if you were traumatized.
Were you traumatized by Mr. Optimist po
dying and your little kid showing you?
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. You're fine.
It's okay. It's okay. They're there.
I'll try not to tease you too hard.
There you go. Where's this one?
Uh, let's put it there.
There you go. My apologies. I bring you
flowers to apologize with my lady.
[laughter]
I'm a bully, but you got Come on now. I
thought you wanted a bully. You saw goth
girl and said, "Oh, I want her to step
on me. I want her to bully me. I don't
want her to be a dork. I want her to cry
mascara. I want her to stab me. And now
I bully you and you complain on nose.
Someone's never met the goth before.
Sip. Welcome. Welcome.
You prefer a dorky.
You want me to be happy? Thank you.
That's so sweet of you.
You [snorts] don't want that. You better
not. Oh my gosh. Imagine if my Imagine
if the snail had mascara.
You like dorky goth girls? I did. I I
did actually know a goth. Was it two
people? No, it was only one. She was
just just kind of normy actually.
I just remember she had a goth boyfriend
and they were both dressed like that. I
don't know what was happening, but I
caught them crying after school before.
I'm pretty sure they probably broke up
or something. I came at a really bad
time. I was there because I was changing
classes and I was like I told him, "Can
you give this to the teacher? Thanks."
and she was like in the middle of crying
to her boyfriend. I think they were
having a very serious conversation and
she was just like, "Well, I got to give
this. I don't want to stay around for
this. Just give it to them. Thanks. I
don't want to get charged for my book.
Thank you, Francisco. Thank you. I did
read the room. I read the room and I
gave them my book."
Guys, just because you read the room
doesn't mean you actually have to follow
the protocol. have to prove to Paul. I
mean,
he was a hot-headed person in movie. He
grows to be like the Matrix of
Leadership that [music] Optimus left
behind.
Huh. Speaking of, I need to make an
evolution chart for you guys.
Sometimes I notice that you guys draw
the novel leads as novel Knights.
They're they're a completely different
species, guys. Well, technically the
same, but it's an evolution chart. Then
again, I guess it is still a novel in
the end.
You do evolve here. Let me let me get my
details.
Let me get a fresh reminder because it
is it is probably the most complicated.
This is probably why people only have
one freaking mascot.
Let me get my details. You got the
novelite right there. Right there. Okay.
And then the next form is actually
the page. That's right. You get the page
right there. That's the your very first
tier for only emotes.
H now the novel is your standard. This
is what everyone looks like as your
standard form. The page is a more of a
magic class user. They actually are able
to float and hover. It's kind of like
rock paper scissors.
And then you have the the bookworm.
Pretty cool. Cool folks. Now, the
bookworm is what most of you guys are.
And they are kind of like the tank.
Really derpy looking. It's kind of funny
cuz I always see the eyes of something
else. I also think of bleach, like the
little holo mask. But no, you're you're
derpy little eyes and it's cute. So
that's what the bookworm is. And then
the final form, of course, is the the
novel knight right here. The novel
knight is the max tier and you guys are
essentially the scissors to everything.
So you got the base baby form. You have
the the wet page to toilet paper page,
but you can cast magic and then you can
become the bookworm. You are a ridable
mount. So, if you ever wanted to feel
what it's like to be ridden by a novel
knight or a page or another bookworm,
you just have to turn into a bookworm.
You guys are a little bit slow, but you
are heavy hitters and novel Knight is a
the mix of both. So, novel Knight is
kind of like you can tank things and
you're fast. And then no is just baby.
Who's just baby? Buy you dinner.
But what if they are the dinner? Oh
yeah, that's that's the the thing. Let
me just make it even.
Um
I don't know how to make this even. You
guys are not like
equal in size.
Shoot. That's okay. I'll just delete
these. There you go. I will now have to
teach you guys that multiple times. Even
management, I will have to teach them. I
will bonk it out of them. They're just
little guys. They're just little guys.
You should get a scale chart. That would
be interesting. Yeah, I guess. We should
probably do a skill chart, huh?
A novel knight can turn. You can
devolve. Yeah, you [laughter] can you
can devolve depending on if your
membership runs out. I mean, yeah, you
could be whatever. You could technically
choose between the forms is what I like
to think.
Funnily enough though, realistically, no
night turn tries to do a baby when they
cancel her membership. [laughter]
It's like a digice, I guess. So,
that would be kind of a cute idea. Okay,
you just gave me an idea.
Maybe.
Yeah, maybe. I'll think about it. Maybe.
There you go. Someone just became a
novel knight. So, some Irish boys,
welcome. Thanks for becoming a novel
knight. And Andrew as well. Look at
that. that someone became they turned
from baby to not so baby now.
Pay to win. No, you could be a novely.
You're just tiny. You're little little.
There you are. There you are. Bouncing
up and down. Oh, you can go on my head.
You're kind of like a hat.
Ingram, thank you so much for the
gifties. There you go. Someone was kind
enough to evolve your asses. [laughter]
You are now a bookworm. Bulgrim has
access to membership post and like just
trivia really and streams.
I'm I'm pretty generous with my
memberships, I think, cuz I I just give
it to like all members except for Novel
Night videos. Those are a little bit
more special. Retro, thank you for the
gifts. And Fox, welcome back. And time
ago, like man, I freaking miss Digimon.
I hate Adrian so much. I hate Annori the
most. I hope they make a new game where
there's no character that steals your
spotlight.
Cats, welcome back. Thanks for becoming
a novel knight. X, what do you mean?
Keen, thanks for becoming a Thanks for
the gifts.
You love Digimon.
I I love Digimon so much, too. I just
hate Aimon specifically. Whatever. She's
not a bad girl. She's the worst girl.
You're right. She's not a bad girl.
She's the worst. Despicable. So
disgusting.
You love the design of the novels and
pages. Oh, nice. Thank you. Paso or Paso
Zenfang V uh Vijay
Jose. Thank you.
All right. Well, I think I'm going to go
back to my pacing. Tomorrow, we're going
to have a watch along. So, please get
your Street Fighters movie going and
then we're going to go play a fun little
game, Mecca Chameleon. Just kind of
taking it easy this week. And then next
week, we're going to have some collabs.
Three of them, Lil Hope, and Resident
Evil 5.
Yippee. Legion, F11, and Court. Thank
you. I hope you guys had a great time at
the concert. I'm so glad that you made
fun memories. And if you did not get to
go to the concert, you can still get
your stream tickets and get the bod when
it is available.
And I will see you guys tomorrow. And um
let's go play Street Fighters at some
point.
Whatever, guys. Um it's not like I'm
I I don't I just like Street Fighter 6.
Okay. I just just a little bit. Just I
just like it a little bit, you know?
Just let's go play story mode and let's
go play a little bit more. It's
whatever. All right, I got to now
respectfully cover you up, my lady.
Where are you?
All right, I will now be your towel, my
little lady. Novelite. Um, novel boys.
[laughter]
Bye.
Moisturizing with me. Oh, you're so well
glistened. [music]
>> [music]
[music]
[bell]